字
字幕
字幕調
字幕調效
字幕調效：
字幕調效：l
字幕調效：la
字幕調效：lai
字幕調效：laix
字幕調效：laixy
字
字幕
字幕調
字幕調效
字幕調效：
字幕調效：l
字幕調效：la
字幕調效：lai
字幕調效：laix
字幕調效：laixy
片名：《保鏢》
Kaavalan [The Bodyguard]
我的人生在一列火車上發生了轉折
My life changed only in a rail journey
雖然我只是在中途登上了這列火車
Even if I have got in the middle..
故事從Mettu patti（印度南部一小鎮）開始
..this story begins in Mettu patti
陸軍少校Partha Sarathy的妻子Kanthimathi
The army major Partha Sarathy's wife Kanthimathi..
已經懷胎十月
..is pregnant for 10th month
Mettupatti附近就是我們的村莊Semmanoor
Mettupatti's neighborhood is our village called Semmanoor
Muthu Ramalingam控制著這個村莊
Muthu Ramalingam dominates the village!
是我 Mari 我是你的人
I am Mari speaking! I am your man.
他已經知道了 他會殺了我的
He has come to know it.. He would kill me
- 救救我 - 你在哪里打電話
-Save me. -Where are you talking from?
我在Mettupatti koil大街
..from Mettupatti, Murugan koil street.
老大 別殺我
Sir! Don't kill me
如果是可以信賴的敵人 也許我會饒了他
I can forgive my enemy if he can be trusted.
但如果是個叛徒 就算是我的兄弟 我也不會放過他
I can't forgive a betrayer even if he is my brother.
老大
Sir..
Muthu Ramalingam來到Mettu patti是為了取人性命
Muthu Ramalingam came to the village to take a life!
可是兩條性命因他而得救 這并非出于偶然
But it is not a coincidence that 2 souls were saved because of him
而是神的安排
That was god's calculation
誰給嬰兒取名 嬰兒就會繼承誰的品行
The infant will inherit the behavior of the one who names the infant.
我不希望他像我一樣殘忍兇暴
So I expect him not to be brutal & vicious like me.
他要做個心靜如水的人
He should be a serene and calm soul!
就像孕育了一切的大地
..like the earth which bears everything.
我就以此為他取名
I will name him that.
Bhoominathan（在泰米爾語中是大地的意思）
Bhoominathan.
Ammukutty（女孩名）和Bhoomi Nathan
Ammukutty & Bhoomi Nathan!
為什么你要把名字擦掉
Why do you erase it off?
因為有個女孩的名字和我的名字寫在一起
Because a girl's name is written along with mine.
也許是因為她喜歡你呢
She might have liked you. That's why.
那這是你寫的哦 你就是Ammukutty
So, is it your work? Are you the Ammukutty?
你在哪個班
Which class are you studying?
從小他就是這個樣子
He is like this since the childhood.
喜歡他的女孩子都對他敬而遠之
The girls admire him keeping a distance.
大家都說長大以后想當醫生 工程師或律師 你卻說什么
All want to become a doctor, engineer, or a lawyer. What did you say?
- 你說你想做Shemmanoor Muthu Ramalingam那樣的人 - 是的 老師
-Do you want to become like Shemmanoor Muthu Ramalingam? -Yes sir
他給嬰兒取這名字是希望他心懷寧靜
He named the child so that he should be serene looking!
可是Bhoominathan卻
..but Bhoominathan
Bhoomi歡迎儀式還行吧
Bhoomi! How's the reception?
- 歡迎誰 - 當然是你嘍
-For whom? -lt's for you!
還不錯 有個家伙和我名字一樣
Not bad. There is a guy in my name!
不是別人 叫的就是你
It is not somebody. lt is only you
去打倒他 把他塞進去
Go and get him. Send him in
- 你 - 快上
-You! -Go I say
他怎么倒了
How did he fall?
- 我們賺了150萬盧比 - 我什么都沒做啊
-15 lakhs are ours! -l didn't do anything.
他有超能力不
Is he get any supernatural power?
好像背扭傷了
It seems there is a sprain in the back
是我贏了
It is me
還有個人
There is another man.
怎么了
What happened?
我以為只是玩玩 沒想到他真打啊
I thought it is a game only. But he is really hitting me!
那你也真打 別浪費時間
You too go. Don't waste any time.
瞧瞧 我拿一成半 剩下的都歸你
Look! 15 percent is mine as commission! The rest is yours.
拿去給你姐姐辦嫁妝吧
Use it for your sister's marriage!
以后別叫我做這種事了
Don't call me for such things any more!
嗎
Mom!
老媽
Mother..
你回來了啊
Have you come?
你這些天都跑哪去了啊
Where were you all this time?
我說過我去了
I told you before I went..
我去參加朋友Shiva他姐姐的婚禮了
..that I am going to my friend Shiva's sister's marriage!
婚禮在Kumbakonam 你跑到曼谷去做什么
Marriage is in Kumbakonam! Why did you go to Bangkok before that?
你兒子一直是本地的小混混
Your son were being a rogue locally!
- 現在開始混到國外去了 - 我
Now he has started to go abroad! I am..
- 舅舅 - 你干嘛老是要我操心啊
-Uncle! -Why are you bothering me?
- 他說的都是真的 - 是真的 老媽
-ls it true what he says? -Yes mom!
干得好
Well done
你去賽拳就是為了錢
He was in the competition to earn money.
總有一天他會為了錢去殺人
He would become a killer just for money.
這就是我的命
It is my fate.
我早就知道
I thought when he named the child..
讓Muthu Ramalingam給孩子取名 孩子一定會繼承他的惡性
I was sure he would inherit the qualities of Muthu Ramalingam.
他已經不做違法勾當了
He has stopped the criminal activities.
他現在是村莊的保護傘
..and has become the Godman of his village.
他必須要讓這個孩子轉性
He has to make this guy good.
我一直在這么想
That's what I was thinking about.
以后再也不能讓他做違法的事了
No criminal activities from him, are allowed in future here.
帶著這條笨狗 我到現在都沒找到家
I couldn't find this address yet..
他必須要讓這個孩子轉性
..when I am searching with this dog.
再這樣下去 我都要累成狗樣了
If I go like this, I'll be exhausted like this dog.
我覺得這里就是了
I think that it is the one.
- 這里就是Bhoomi - 叫他Bhoomi老大
-This is Bhoomi.. -Call him Bhoomi sir.
誰要是再敢直呼他的英名
If anyone calls him only his name hereafter..
就要承擔一切惡果
..he will face the consequences.
這不是間房子 這是間寺廟
This is not a house but a temple.
他不是Bhoomi 他是我的大神
He is not Bhoomi but my Samy(God).
Bhoomi出來吧
Bhoomi! Come out.
那是誰 老爸 是你朋友嗎
Who is it dad? Is he your friend?
我是你的助手
I am your Assistant!
讓我留下來做你的助手吧 你的生命會因此而閃耀
Keep me as your assistant! Your life will be bright.
- 你是誰 - 噢 天哪
-Who are you? -Oh god!
我跪著 你卻站在邊上看
You are watching while I am bowing down.
你和我一起跪 這樣才會答應我們留下來
You too have to bow down. Only then we both can be with him!
- 老大 狗狗的埔士不錯吧 - 站起來
-Boss! How is my dog's pose? -Get up!
我不起來 你得接受我
I won't. You have to commit me
- 接受我 - 那是誰啊
-Commit -Who is that?
為什么一大清早就堵在我們家門口
He has come and blocked the way in the early morning!
- 我有么 - 給我起來
-Am l like that? -Hey, get up man
我有問過你要助手嗎
Did I ask you for an assistant?
難道人們為Muruga神削發也要征得同意
（Muruga：印度教戰神 也被稱為泰米爾人之神）
Does one tonsure his head for Lord Murugan?
難道出席葬禮穿喪服也要遺體同意
Does one wear dress seeing the body?
同樣我不需要你的同意就能做你的保鏢
Like wise I have joined as a bodyguard for you without your permission
告訴我 你要我去砍誰
Tell me now. You show me him now
我立馬就去把他剁了
I will chop him off then and there.
他問你呢 告訴他
He is asking you. Tell him.
- 鼓起勇氣來 - 讓他砍我吧
-Take courage! -Let him chop me away.
砍他
Is it him?
你還嫌這里不夠亂啊 走開
He is adding more problems! Go
我能把包和狗留下嗎
Can l leave the bag and dog here?
它看著就像條流浪狗
He looks like a street dog!
嗨 你可以侮辱我 但你不能侮辱我兄弟
Look! You can abuse me, but not my brother
它不是你說的流浪狗
He is not a street dog as you say.
你瞧著 我來證明它是頭雄獅
You can watch it. I will prove that he is a lion!
這是個球兄弟
This is a ball. Brother.
好了 真不錯
That's it. Fine!
瞧見了嗎 老大
Have you seen it boss?
它把球撿回來了
He has brought back the ball!
我整整整訓練了他3年
I gave him training for 3 years for this act.
3年才教會它撿球
3 years for retrieving the ball?
你自己只要一分鐘就能把球撿回來
You could bring it in 2 minute as well!
- 老大 瞧瞧這是什么 - 一把劍
-Boss! What is this? -A sword!
我當年在Koduva Kummattha手下做事
When l was working with Koduva Kummattha..
因為事情做得很棒 他賞給我這把劍
..he gave me this gift for my good performance!
這是Pitchuva Pakiri賞給我的
It is the gift Pitchuva Pakiri gave me!
這是炸彈 Baskar給我的禮物 他怕了我了
This is the gift which Bomb Baskar gave me after he got afraid of me!
- 禮物 - 炸彈
-Gift? -Bomb!
你拉這里 然后丟出去
If you pull this ring and throw it..
能炸爛一堆人
..a group will reduce to ruins!
拉這里不
Is it the one?
靠 它會爆炸的
Damn it. It will get blasted.
- 那就把它扔了唄 - 沒錯
-Throw it if it would blast! -Yes..
噢 天哪
Oh god!
- 喔 我的兄弟叼起來了 - 啊 神哪
-Whoa! My brother took it. -Oh god!
他要叼回來還給我
He is coming to return to me!
老大 救救我
Boss! Please save me.
它改變路線了
He has changed the route.
這不是包子 這是炸彈 快扔掉
It is not a bun but a bomb! Throw it down.
鬼啊 妖怪啊
Ghost.. Devil..
狗啊
Dog..
來了 大兄弟 你在哪里
Come brother! Where are you?
我在這兒
I am here.
大兄弟來了
Brother has come
大兄弟 你手上拿的是什么
What in law.. with a cover in your hand?
是調你去Shemmanoor的調令
Is it the transfer to Shemmanoor?
不是 是保護令
No. Protection duty!
Semmanoor Muthu Ramalingam有生命危險
Semmanoor Muthu Ramalingam's life is in danger!
他們要調我去那里保護他
So for his protection they have transferred me to there.
Muthanna有生命危險 出什么事了
Is Muthanna's life in danger? What happened?
妹夫 只要你打個電話給他
In-law! If you call Muthu Ramalingam and tell him..
他肯定會拒絕警方保護
..he would refuse to take police protection.
那我們的擔子就算放下了
Our burden will be eased off.
舅舅 你還算是個警察嗎
Uncle! Are you a true policeman?
上頭給你保護任務 你卻想逃避
When you are given the escort duty you tend to escape from that.
把命令給我 我去保護他
Give me the order! I'll go to protect him.
這沒什么好爭的 這是公務
This is not any disputes to solve. This is the department matter.
這是要求保護生命的政府公務
This is the government order to protect a life.
就算讓我去 那也是對命令的尊重
Even if I go, it will be a respect for the order.
你管這個干什么 不要多管閑事
Why do you need all these? You mind your business.
爸 沒有他 我和老媽還能站在你面前嗎
Dad! He is the reason why my mom and me are alive now.
現在他有生命危險 我怎么能束手旁觀
I can't keep idle when l know that his life is in danger.
你干嘛把那封信交給他
Why did you give the letter to him?
他要是起疑 拆開來看了怎么辦
What if he reads it after getting the doubt?
他不會對自己相信的人起疑的
He won't doubt anyone whom he believes!
也不會背叛他們的
..or betray them!
我的外甥品質如此
That's the quality of my nephew!
SEMMANOOR Municipality村歡迎你
SEMMANOOR Municipality. Welcomes you!
快上來 往里擠
Come up! Climb up!
拿好票 零頭待會找
Take it. Give the change later
你去哪
Where are you going?
我去Semmanoor Muthuramalingm家執行保護任務
I'm going to Semmanoor Muthuramalingm's house on protection duty.
過來坐這吧 我讓位子給你
You come and sit here. I'll get up.
不 不 還是你坐吧
No. You can sit there.
我馬上下車了 你坐吧
I'll get down now
把小孩給我 我讓他坐我腿上
Give the baby to me. I'll put it on my lap!
沒事的 你坐下
It's okay, you sit down!
沒事的 坐我腿上好了
It's ok! I'll put it on my lap
她和我打招呼 然后又叫我坐在她腿上
She called me.. and then asking me to sit on her lap.
還等什么快來
Why do you hesitate? Come
不行啊 車上人太多了
No. The bus is crowded.
我們私底下再坐吧
We shall have it in privacy!
- 和你說了 過來吧 - 這可不行
-Tell you to come to me. -This won't work out.
- 我得表現得有種些 - 快來 快過來 - 來了 來了 別急
-l have to show my worth. -Come. Come to me. -Coming. Don't be hurry
這樣看上去不錯吧 你叫什么叫啊
Does it look good? Why do you yell up?
- 狗日的 快起來 - 出什么事了
-Damn it! Get up -What happened?
聽我解釋 要打連她一塊兒打
Listen to me.. Beat her too
聽我說 我的老大在那邊看著呢
Look.. My boss is looking
他來這里干什么 欠揍啊
Why has he come here and getting beaten up?
你知道你打的是誰嗎
Do you know who you are beating?
你打的是警察 一位要去
You have beaten the police officer who is..
Semmanoor Muthu Ramalingam家保護他的警察
..going to Semmanoor Muthu Ramalingam's house for protection!
我不是一個人 從在那里的那位警官
I'm not alone. The inspector who is sitting there..
是和我一起的
..is coming with me.
- 為什么他需要保護 - 因為他有生命危險
-Why does he need protection? -His life is in danger!
他是去當保鏢的
He is going as his bodyguard.
我是負責護送他的
I am going with him as an escort.
你打我就等于打他
You are beating him without knowing it.
你去請求他原諒你
You ask him to pardon you.
否則我把你們全射死在車里
Or else, I'll shoot down all in the bus!
警官 我剛才不知道您是誰才問您收車票錢的
Sir! I issued the ticket without knowing who you are.
請收回你的錢
Please get back your money.
走開 走開
Go man! Move away.
- 轉過身去 - 沒問題
-Turn back. -l will.
媽啊
Mom!
要是你再跟著我 靠
If you come behind me again.. Oh god!
- Valli妹妹 Meera在哪里呢 - 她在樓上
-Valli sister. Where is Meera? -She is upstairs.
你在哪里
Where are you?
你家來了個保鏢
A bodyguard has come to your house.
保鏢 為什么
Bodyguard? Why?
你爸爸有生命危險
Your dad's life is in danger.
保鏢是來保護他的
The bodyguard has come for his protection!
是誰胡說八道
Who has told this foolishness?
胡說八道 是我爸告訴我的
Foolishness? My dad has told me that.
你爸走著路都能睡著
He sleeps when he walks!
也許是他說夢話胡扯來著
He would have blabbered this in his dream!
這里就是Semmanoor府邸 進來吧
This is the Semmanoor place. Please come.
Muthu Ramalingam就生于此長于此
This is where Muthu Ramalingam was born and brought up.
他現在不在家 他在迪拜
He is not here now. He is in Dubai.
你坐今晚的航班回印度 然后就回家
He will come in the evening flight. He will be here after that.
- 先生 - 請進
-Sir! -Please come.
- 請進 這是女主人Devika太太 - 您好
-Please come. She is his wife! Devika madam. -Greetings!
他是來保護主人的 他是Mohan Raj警官
He has come for the protection of sir! He is Inspector Mohan Raj.
先生 我叫Bhoomi Nathan
Bhoomi Nathan, sir!
我叫Chakrapani 我是主人唯一的管家
Chakrapani, I'm the only manager to sir!
我很警覺 就算是影子都潛不進來
I am very alert that even a shadow wouldn't enter here.
這里沒有他的仇人
When there are no enemies for him in this place..
我不知道為什么他需要人來保護
..I wonder why he needs a protection!
- Chakra兄弟 - 我正要問他
-Chakra brother! -l was asking that to him.
他在這里有仇家嗎
Does he have any enemies here?
危險不僅僅來自于仇家
Danger can come not only from the enemies!
有時危險就來自于周圍的人
But it can be from the people around.
這是屋子的大廳
This is the main hall of this house!
- 他就是那個保鏢 - 沒錯
-ls he the bodyguard? -Yes!
- 你說什么 - 她就是主人的女兒Meera
-What? -She is sir's daughter Meera!
Meera 他把我當成你了
Meera! He took me for you!
就那樣好
Let it be like that.
- 先生 - 來來 我們到處看看
-Sir! -Come. Let's go around the house.
他往這邊來了
He is coming
- 這里是院子 - 看看 他像個保鏢嗎
-This is the court yard. -Look! ls he like the bodyguard?
他就像個男仆一樣要看遍我們的家
He wants to go around our home like the groom
只要我在這里 就沒什么進得了這個屋子
Nothing will enter into this house still I am here
主人的房間在樓上
Sir's room is in the upstairs
哦 天哪
Oh god!
是誰
Who is it?
誰扎破了氣球 是誰
Who has cracked he balloon? Who?
- 你盯著我看什么 - 不是我
-Why do you stare at me? -lt is not me.
是你自己睡著了
It's you after your sleep.
一支箭
An arrow!
從哪里來的
Where has it come from now?
從我頭上拿下來的嗎
Is it from my head?
作哦一名保鏢 你應該帶著勇氣而來
As a bodyguard, you should've come with energy (Thembu).
而不是帶著箭（泰米爾語中勇氣是Thembu 箭是Ambu 讀音近似）
..not with an arrow (ambu)
他看上去身手不錯哦
He looks very smart!
他過來了 快躲起來 快
He is coming! Escape. Go.
噢 快
Oops! Go..
- 那我去機場接主人了 - 行 你去吧
-l'll meet sir in the airport -Ok. You may go.
- 你是誰 - 她嗎 - 她在Meera的廠里做工
-Who are you? -She..! -She works in Meera's factory!
那她為什么在這里而不待在廠里
Why is she here instead of the factory?
我們是來看你的
We have come to see you.
- 看我 - 我們還從沒親眼參觀過保鏢呢
-Why? -We haven't seen a bodyguard as a whole.
你在開玩笑吧 我看著像個小丑嗎
Are you teasing? Do I look like a buffoon?
為了安全起見 未經允許 誰都不許踏進這個院了
None is allowed to come unnecessarily to this compound.
你憑什么這么說 我們會經常來的
We will come at times! Who are you to tell that?
這個油腔滑調的是誰 你們的工會主席嗎
Who is this smarty? Is it the union leader?
在廠里隨你怎么玩 在這里不行
You can have this nonsense in your factory. Not here.
啊 我的頭要炸了
Whoa! My head has exploded!
他們打中我了 把我打死了
They have shot me! Shot me! Shot me to death.
MADURAI機場
MADURAI AIRPORT
哈 那是我的人
Whao! lt's my man.
他去哪里了
Where has he gone?
剛才還在這里的
He was here.
- 你來這里做什么 - 什么 老大 你干了什么
-What is going on? -What boss? What have you done?
Muthu Ramalingam和他兒子要坐飛機來了
Muthu Ramalingam and his son are coming in the flight.
我們必須要保證安全 對嗎
We have to provide security for them, right?
那沒錯 可現在又沒下雨
It is ok. lt is not raining now.
- 你穿著雨衣做什么 - 雨衣
-Why do you wear a rain coat? -Rain coat?
這是獨一無二的裝備
This is an unique outfit.
有大用途的外套
A dress with good sense!
磁力外套
Magnetic dress!
- 磁力外套 - 沒錯 老大
-Magnetic dress? -Yes boss
這就是磁力外套
The magnetic dress
只要機場里有任何鐵質的武器 它都能找出來
This dress will find out the iron weapons if any in this airport!
暴露在我們的面前
It can reveal them to us!
啊 我的天哪
Oh my God!
一支槍貼在我身上
A rifle is on my body
快拉開
Pull it out.
快掰下來
Snatch it away.
你算什么警察 快掰開來
What a police you are! Snatch it away
靠 我讓你掰下來 你開什么槍啊
Damn it. You are shooting instead of snatch it.
天哪 別開槍
Oh god! Don't shoot
把槍口朝天上
Place it in upward direction
完了
Oops!
謝天謝地
Thank god!
老大 你吩咐
Tell me boss.
Muthu Ramalingam出來了 干掉他
Muthu Ramalingam is coming out. Finish him.
是 老大
OK sir.
爸 出什么事了
Dad! What happened?
有人跑過來把我撞翻了
Someone came running and hit against me.
我們走
Let's go.
他在哪里 怎么沒見到人
Where is he? ..not to be seen!
你看不見 他在后面
Can't you see? He is there.
我不是問Karthi
I didn't ask for Karthi!
- 我是問那個保鏢 - 誰 - 那個保鏢
-l was asking for the bodyguard. -Who? -lt is him
他去機場接機了 你沒看到他嗎
He has come to receive you in the airport. Didn't you see him?
你去洗把臉吧 總是說夢話
Wash your face! You are always sleeping!
我沒說夢話
I don't say in the sleep.
真的 你的保鏢來了
Really your bodyguard has come.
- 保鏢 - 是的
-Bodyguard? -Yes
我為什么要保鏢
Why do I need a bodyguard?
爸爸 你有生命危險
Dad! Your life is in danger!
他受命而來的
He was ordered to come.
是的 所以我們安排他住在外屋了
Yes! That's why he has been allotted space in the out house.
你們不長腦子的嗎
Don't you have sense?
陌生人說什么就是什么
You believe strangers what they say!
他們要什么就給什么嗎
..and provide what they ask for, right?
主人 我在 有何吩咐
Sir! I am here. Tell me.
我不需要什么保鏢
I don't need a bodyguard.
- 不管他是誰 打發他走 聽到了嗎 - 好的 主人
-Send them back whoever it is. OK? -Right sir.
爸爸就是那樣的 別打發他走
Dad is like that. Don't send them back.
我們需要那樣的人保護我們的安全
We need a guy like that for our safety.
我會和爸爸說的 好嗎
I'll talk to dad, ok?
父親要他走 女兒不要他走
Dad wants him to go back and daughter is against him!
這種情況下 我怎么還睡得著
How can I have my sleep in this situation?
工會主席 你在這里做什么
You union leader! What are you doing here?
下班后你該回自己的家
You have to go back to your home after the work!
我回去了 女主人要我來了
I went. Madam asked me to come!
所以我就來了
That's why I came here.
女主人要你來 那你該去那個房間
You go to that room if mom asked to come..
你去少爺房間干什么
Why do you go to his room?
- 因為 - 別是出軌的事吧
-That is.. -Are you acting big?
都是因為惹上了女人的事 他才離開這里的
He went out of town in the ladies weakness!
現在才剛回來
..and he has come only now!
你還想惹新的麻煩嗎
Do you want to create problem again?
你說什么 什么女人的事
What did you say? Ladies weakness?
是啊 大學里
Yes, In college..
到這邊說
Come here.
大學里的時候 他和一個女生扯上了關系
When he was in the college, he got linked up with a girl..
惹出了大麻煩
..and created a big problem!
那女孩的父親把他抓去 逼他和自己的女兒成親
Her dad took him and was about to forcibly marry him to his daughter!
我們的主人想辦法把他救出來了 送去迪拜
Our sir managed to save him from that and sent him to Dubai!
一個保鏢怎么會知道這些事
How do the bodyguard know all this?
你覺得保鏢就該一無所知嗎
Do you think that a bodyguard is nothing?
我知道保鏢的全部歷史
I know the complete history of the bodyguard..
還有敵人會怎樣找上門來
.. and how the enemies could come!
我用拳腳就能打退他門
I could get rid of them by force only then!
要是對方也很歷害呢
What if he too is strong?
那 我們就要更歷害 把他消滅
Then.. we have to use more strength and destroy him!
你反問我做什么
Why do you ask cross questions?
只有動物才用暴力制服其他動物
Only animals use their power to rule over other animals!
- 什么 - 我們要用愛而不是用武力來改變別人
-What? -We have to use love not strength to correct man!
好 我同意 這么晚了
Ok! I agree. You need not have to rule others..
你不需要用愛來制服誰 走吧
..in this night with love! Go..
Meera 進來
Come Meera!
你曾經愛過一個女孩 后來背叛了她
You have loved & betrayed a girl before.
所以爸爸才送你去迪拜
That's why you were sent to Dubai.
- 誰和你說的 - 那個女孩
-Who told you all this? -lt was that girl!
她打電話給我了 電話里都告訴我了
She called me over phone and told this!
那不是真的 她在撒謊
It is a lie. She was lying!
你才在撒謊 我現在就打電話給她
You are lying I'll call her now
讓她明早就帶著自己的東西過來
and ask her to come with her belongings in the morning.
- 別那么做 - 我現在就打
-Don't do it. -l will call her.
聽我說
Listen to what I say.
媽
Mom!
- 站住 - 他一來就惹麻煩
-Stop! -He has started the moment he arrived.
- 站住 -看上去關于他的傳聞都是真的
-Stop! -It looks like what l heard about him is true!
站住
Stop..
他奶奶的
Damn him.
站住
Stop
哦 天哪
Oh god!
- 你走吧 我來搞定他 - 你搞什么鬼啊
-You can go, I'll take care of him. -What have you done?
他是我哥哥
He is my brother!
我是Meera Muthu Ramalingam的女兒
I'm Meera, Muthu Ramalingam's daughter!
快走 別讓其他人看見你
Go. See that others don't watch you!
- 老哥 - 你沒聽見我說嗎
-Brother! -Didn't you hear me?
快離開這
Go from here and fast.
發生什么事了
What has happened there?
- 什么聲音 - 我不知道 太太
-What is the sound there? -l don't know mom.
剛才我在那里看見Meera
Just now I met Meera there..
要是我爸看見你 他不會讓你活著離開的 快走
If he sees you.. he won't let you go alive! Go..
啊 出什么事了
Whoa! What happened?
- 到底出什么事了 - 媽 是這樣
-What has happened here? -Mom, that is..
別愣著 去端些水來
Don't stand there idle. Bring some water.
老哥
Brother!
- 太太 水來了 - 遞給我
-Here madam -Give it to me
老哥
Brother..
出什么事了 剛才是什么聲音
What happened? What is the sound there?
Karthi出什么事了
What went wrong with Karthi?
他在前面跑 Meera在后面追他玩
He ran and she chased him for fun
不當心就在臺階上摔倒了
He fell down by accident in the steps..
晚上黑不溜秋的 很容易摔跤
If you run in the dark you would fall by accident.
他們不是小孩子 這么容易摔跤嗎
Are they children to fall down for that?
爸 不是的 我不是不當心摔倒的
No dad! I didn't fall by accident.
有人從背后揍我
Somebody has beaten me from behind!
誰這么大膽 敢在這間屋子里打少爺
Who has the courage to beat you in this house?
有人從背后揍你
Has somebody beaten you from behind!
- 到底是誰 - 是我
-Who is that? -lt was me.
我看見Meera邊跑邊喊 所以才打他的
I beat him when I saw her running, crying!
我給你的房間在外面
I gave you bed only there.
你怎么進到里屋來了
How did you come inside?
- 他是誰 - 就是他 我們的保鏢
-Who is he? -lt is him, our bodyguard!
嗯 我就是那個保鏢
Yes! I'm the bodyguard!
爸爸 不要 他是無辜
Dad No. He is innocent.
我說謊騙他玩
I told a lie for fun.
他相信了才會打我老哥的
He believed that and beat our brother!
我和你說過不能留他
I told you before not to allow him.
陌生人進來揍了你哥哥
Some stranger came and beat your brother!
這就是你所謂的保鏢的責任
Is it your bodyguard duty?
我和你說過我們不要什么保鏢 把他押送回去
I told you we don't need anybody guard and to send him back!
你要是再把事情搞砸 你也一樣給我滾出去
If you can't do your duty, you could as well leave from here
主人 我想說 主人
Sir.. what I want to tell.. Sir..
不管你是誰 以后再也不準回來這里
Don't come back to this place whoever you are.
你要是敢再來 滾
If you come.. go away.
- 爸 - 什么事
-Dad! -Tell me.
他走的時候把這封信留給了管家大叔
This letter was given to uncle when he left this place.
他為什么把信收下來
Why did he get it from him?
讓他把信撕了
Tell him to tear it off.
他說他和你很熟
He said he knows you well.
他說是你給他取的名字 Bhoomi Nathan
He said that you have christened him! Bhoomi Nathan!
Bhoomi Nathan!
Bhoomi Nathan
致Semmanoor Muthannan
To Semmanoor Muthannan!
寫信人Mettupatti Parthasarathy
..from Mettupatti Parthasarathy!
攜信人是犬子Bhoominathan
The bearer of this letter is my son Bhoominathan.
我們騙他說你有生命危險
He was sent to you by telling a lie..
將他騙至你身邊 請原諒我們
..that your life is in danger! Forgive me.
不這么說的話 他是不會來的
Other wise he wouldn't have come there.
他會一直混跡街頭當個混混
He would be roaming like a rouge!
只有你才能讓他改邪歸正
Only you can make him come good.
非常感謝 Parthasarathy
..with thanks, Parthasarathy.
Chakrapani在哪
Where is Chakrapani?
讓他把Bhoominathan帶回來 去吧
Ask him to bring him back. Go.
一位統治天
One is ruling the sky
一位統治地
..and one for the earth.
統治你我的 那是全能的神
The one who rules me and you, is almighty.
一位統治天
One is ruling the sky
一位統治地
..and one for the earth.
統治你我的 那是全能的神
The one who rules me and you, is almighty.
九洲大地皆富裕
The wealthy are there in every place.
萬民大眾皆平等 那是完美無缺的神
One who treats everyone as equal is the flawless one!
父母雙親勝于神
The parents are superior than God.
秀出真正的舞蹈來
Show what is the real dance!
一位統治天
One is ruling the sky
一位統治地
..and one for the earth.
統治你我的 那是全能的神
The one who rules me and you, is almighty.
大步邁向前 終會贏盛名
Go forward and you will gain good name.
世界屬于我們
The place is all ours.
大膽無畏 大愛無疆
Be courageous! Be lovable!
人生何處無起伏
The ups and downs are there in the life.
舞出節奏 舞出速度 舞出和諧來
Dance with rhythm, speed and tune.
大家聚起來 一起來舞蹈
Gather the crowd and make dance
帶著滿腔愛 供慶此節日
With love, let's celebrate the fete with our relatives
眾人皆逐盛名 吾欲做舞中之王
All are after good name and is the king in dance.
歡天喜地舞起來
Let's dance with joy!
一位統治天
One is ruling the sky
一位統治地
..and one for the earth.
統治你我的 那是全能的神
The one who rules me and you, is almighty.
誰人在你心中
Who is in your mind?
哪位是他配偶
Tell me who his pair is!
Radha心中的 只有主Krishna
（Krishna是印度教大神毗濕奴的化身之一）
Lord Krishna is in the mind of Radha!
此地滿溢喜慶 遍地馳騁禮車
（印度教節日中 會以二輪禮車搭載神象）
The place is full of festivity along with is Thiruvaroor chariot!
Iyyanar 無需山羊作為犧牲
（Iyyanar是印度教中農村的保護神）
Iyyanar won't demand goat as sacrifice!
愛是通用的語言
Love's language, way all are same.
全世界通用的語言
It is same in the world!
讓愛的旗幟飛揚 讓我們的步伐向前
Let the flag of love fly and we will go forward.
恐懼將會消失 從此無影無蹤
Fear should vanish! ..and should be removed.
世上只存勇往直前
Let boldness rule the earth.
大地隨歌舞動 歌聲占滿大地
The place will dance for my song & rule the place!
你可留下喜訊
You could leave a good news!
一位統治天
One is ruling the sky
一位統治地
..and one for the earth.
統治你我的 那是全能的神
The one who rules me and you, is almighty.
九洲大地皆富裕
The wealthy are there in every place.
萬民大眾皆平等 那是完美無缺的神
One who treats everyone as equal is the flawless one!
父母雙親勝于神
The parents are superior than God.
秀出真正的舞蹈來
Show what is the real dance!
- 是我 Bhoomi - 什么事 Bhoomi
-Bhoomi is speaking! -What Bhoomi?
不要靠近車子
Don't go near the car!
- 車里有炸彈 - 車里有什么
-There is bomb in the car! -ln the car?
有人在車里放了炸彈
Yes! Somebody has planted a bomb in the car.
你不明白你在說什么
I don't understand what you are telling!
不要靠近車子 車里有炸彈
Don't go near the car. There is a bomb in the car.
我還是聽不明白
I don't understand what you are telling.
- 回來再說吧 - 主人
-Tell it when we are at home. -Sir!
- Karthi 你和爸一起走 - 好的 老爸
-Karthi! You come with mom. -Ok dad.
你和他一起去
You go with him
- Karthi - 主人
-Bhoomi! -Sir!
這算什么 快住手
What is all this? Stop it.
啊 媽
Oh mom!
哦 Meera
Whoe! Meera!
快過來
Come.
媽 在Semmanoor就算是森林都不會和我們作對
Mom! Even Semmanoor forest won't be against us.
都是因為你 才帶來了暴力
Because of you it has lead to violence.
在主人看見你之前離開這里
Leave this place before he sees you.
否則你會死無葬身之地 我們走
Or else you will drop dead. Come.
主人 我們可以進去把他揍得稀巴爛
Sir! We can go in and hack, whack or do anything to him.
可是那個愛著Karthi的女孩已經自殺了
But the girl who loved Karthi committed suicide.
誰稀罕你的仁慈
Who wants his mercy?
你的仁慈能讓我的女兒復活嗎
Will my girl come alive just for your mercy?
你兒子胡做非為 就能逍遙法外嗎
Will the atrocity of your son become unnoticed?
我再說一遍 我兒子沒有胡作非為
I repeat what I say. My son didn't do any atrocity.
是你女兒發瘋似的愛上了他
It was your girl who was madly in love with him.
是你的傲慢自大斷送了她的性命
It was your arrogance which caused your girl's death.
你怪在我兒子頭上 還想毀了我的全家
By blaming my son, you wanted to ruin my family.
我對你客氣不是因為我怕你
It is not because I am afraid that I am being polite to you.
是他讓我冷靜下來 帶我到這里
He has made me calm and brought me here.
就此打住吧
Stop it here.
不要讓我又變成以前的Muthu Ramalingam
Don't change me as the old Muthu Ramalingam.
我遭受的一切痛苦 我會讓你一一嘗到的
I will make you suffer as l suffer now.
你會親眼看到你女兒的死亡
You are going to watch the death of your daughter.
成功到來不停頓 只因有你
Success will come to me non-stop.
你可因此而自豪
You can be proud to be the reason for it.
你到車里去干什么 快出來
Why do you get in the car? Come out.
老大 你可不能再驅趕我了
Boss! You can't chase me anymore.
我要當你的助手 你卻把我趕走
You send me away whenever I ask you for a job.
現在我找到捷徑了 我成了這家子的女婿
Taking a short cut, I became internal son-in-law of this house
你成了這家子的女婿嗎
Are you the internal son-in-law of the house?
別緊張 親愛的Poongodi
Don't get tensed. Poongodi dear!
- 過來下 - 什么事 - 過來下 親愛的
-Come here. -What is it? -Come here, dear!
告訴老大我是誰
Tell sir who I am.
他是 他是我的未婚夫
He is.. he is my fiance!
他向我求婚 然后我把他介紹給了主人
After the proposal I took him to sir and introduced him!
主人讓他做家里的司機
He offered him the driver's job.
- 消失吧 - 消失 你丟了什么
-lt is gone. -Gone? What did you lose?
你給我消失吧 閉嘴
You! Close the shop!
保鏢 主人叫你去
Bodyguard! Sir is calling you.
- 主人 你叫我 - 是的
-Sir! Did you call me? -Yes.
把你大學時的詳細信息和證書交給Karthi
Give your details & certificates of your college to Karthi!
我已經安排你和Meera進同一所大學
I have arranged for admission for you in the college where Meera is studying!
你要我進大學讀書嗎 不行啊 主人
Do you want to admit me in the college? No sir.
我不讀書已經很多年了
It is long time since I stopped my studies.
我不想讀書了
I don't want to study anymore!
誰管你讀不讀書
Who is bothered about your studies?
你是去保護Meera的
You will be the bodyguard for Meera.
保護Meera
..as Meera's bodyguard?
沒錯 Meera和我女兒Madhu假期后
Yes! Meera and my daughter Madhu are going to college...
要去讀大學了
..after the vacation!
主人決定讓你作為保鏢陪她們去
Sir has decided that you have to go with them as their bodyguard!
主人 恕我直言 我的責任是保護你
Sir! Don't mistake me. It is my duty to be your bodyguard.
可是要我去保護一個女孩子
But for a girl.....!
Bhoomi 難道那天你沒聽見Devarajan說的話
Bhoomi! Didn't you hear what Devarajan told the other day?
好吧 主人 我會去的
Ok,sir. I will go.
Chakra別睡了 給他們安排去吧
Chakra! Don't sleep. Make arrangements for them to go.
是 主人 明天你就和她們一起走吧
Ok, Sir. Tomorrow you are going with them.
還有你的未婚夫也要一起去
Along with them your future husband...
瞧瞧他擺的姿勢 他叫什么名字
Look how he gives his pose. What is his name?
-Amavasai - Amavasai和你一起去
-Amavasai! -Amavasai and you are going with them.
- 為什么要他一起去 - 讓你有個伴
-Why do we want him? -Just to accompany you.
你們不住大學宿舍
You are not going to the college hostel.
你們住主人的別墅
But in the guest house of sir.
等一下 Meera已經訂婚了
Wait. Meera's is engaged already.
一定要記住
Keep that in mind always.
- Chakra兄弟 - 啊 沒錯
-Then Chakra brother! -Correct!
他不能像個學校里的學生
He shouldn't behave like a student in the college.
- 他要看上去像個保鏢 - 不用擔心 太太
-He should be a bodyguard! -Don't worry madam.
無論Meera去哪里 我都形影不離
I'll be a shadow for Meera wherever she go.
這才是稱職的保鏢
..like a perfect bodyguard.
第一天報到的新生們
Students who have come for the 1st day of the college..
作為這所學校最勇敢的人 號稱校之雄獅的本人
This university's courageous guy lion of the college.
代表所有人歡迎新生代表
I welcome the leader on behalf of all!
- 嗨 小家伙 -滾
-Hai, buddy. -Get away.
這是個花環嗎 我還以為是個拱門呢
Is it a garland? I thought it was an Arch.
靠
Oops!
你給了我這么重一束花
You give me a heavy one.
你沒腦子嗎
Don't you have sense?
一朵玫瑰花才比較適合我
A rose flower is apt for me.
快點拿給我 有人會拌跤摔死的 拿給我
Take it fast. Someone will against it and die. Take it.
像小山一樣重
It seems like a hill.
- 那是誰 - 等等 我讓你們下車你們再下
-Who is that? -Wait! Get down only after I tell you.
哦 天哪
Oh God!
她穿得可真傻
His outfit looks silly.
大家都在望著我們
All are looking at us.
盡管讓他們看 要讓所有人都知道我是你們的保鏢
Let them watch us. Let them know that l'm your bodyguard.
所以我才穿套制服來的
This uniform is for that only.
你是穿保鏢的衣服跟她們去學校的嗎
Have you gone with them in the bodyguard's attire?
還記得我交待你的話嗎
Do you remember what l told you?
你們現在在哪里 到學校了嗎
Where are you now? Have you reached the college?
是 太太 Meera和Madhu正在去教室的路上
Yes madam! Meera and Madhu are going to their classes!
我正跟隨著她們
I'm going behind them!
你是蠢還是笨啊
Is your duty in the ladies toilet?
先生 那是個
Sir! That is...
不要說了 我不想聽解釋 你隨隨便便就闖了進去
You went there wantonly.
在你以前的學校你就是個不良分子
You were a rowdy in the college you studied.
很多人都和我這樣說了
Many people told me that.
但我還是接受了你入學
But you were given admission in this college.
你知道為什么嗎 因為我看過你的成績單
Do you know why? After seeing your mark sheet only.
你本可以拿第2名的
You could be No.2 in the university..
只要你別混日子 而是好好讀書的話
..if you hadn't been a rowdy in the college and if you studied well.
不過現在在這里 你還是有機會榜上有名的
You have chances to become a rank holder even now.
他在說廢話
He is doing unnecessary talk
只是因為這個原因 我才原諒你這一次
You have been pardoned off for this only reason..
而不是開除你 明白嗎
..without dismissing you! Understand?
要是你再以保鏢的名義進入女廁所
If you go to the ladies toilet again in the pretext of your duty...
沒有你的命令我不會再進去了
I won't go unless you tell me.
- 好 去吧 - 去女廁所嗎
-Ok go. -To the ladies toilet?
去教室
Go to your class.
他總是給我惹麻煩 瞧瞧他
He is bothering me too much. See him!
坐在地板上
Sit down on the floor.
要是桌子斷了 他們會怪我的
If the desk breaks off.. they will blame me.
大家早上好 請坐 請坐
What is this? Go and sit there.
快找位置坐下
The one with a smiling mouth has come.
坐 請坐下
Go and sit.
我讓你坐下
I told you to sit.
為什么 有問題嗎
Why? ls there any problem?
我不應該坐下來 我是一名保鏢
Bodyguards won't sit.
保鏢從來不坐
Bodyguard! What for?
保鏢 保護誰 你叫什么？
What's your name sir?
啊
Whoa!
當心點
Careful..
挪過去點
Move a little.
是 上課時要集中注意力
That is.. You should concentrate in the class!
要是你老是東張西望的 你怎么可能學明白
If you look here and there, you won't be able to understand.
你是來學校讀書的還是來走時裝秀的
Are you coming to the college to study or for the fashion parade?
我沒問你 你是Meera嗎
I didn't ask you! Are you Meera?
- 不管是誰回答 反正你要的就是個答案 - 你閉嘴給我出去
Whoever it is, all you want is the answer!
他是來保護Meera的
He is there for giving protection for Meera.
那誰來保護我
Who will give protection for me?
所以我對你說 要對Bhoomi好一點
That's why I told you to be friendly with Bhoomi!
完全不是那回事
Not at all.
要想讓他融入我們
If he has to be brought in our way as you think..
只有你們女孩子才能辦到
..it could be possible only with you girls.
- 不防試試 - 你不讓我們活了啊
-Just have a try. -Don't you like us being alive?
我沒讓你們去和他當面說
I didn't ask you to go to him and tell.
我是說通過電話
I mean over the phone!
你們知道月多少女孩子在電話里愛上了我嗎
Do you know how many girls love me over the phone?
她們沒一個知道我是誰
None of them know who I am.
這就是電話情緣的優勢
That's the advantage of the love in phone!
安靜 沒人說要通過電話來改變他
Be quiet. None has to change him over the phone.
能讓他不穿制服就足夠了
Tell an idea how to change his uniform. That's enough.
每次看到你的制服我都嫉妒
I feel jealousy when l see your uniform.
你總不給我機會穿一次
You haven't given me a chance to wear this.
- 那至少給我個機會讓我燙一次吧 - 不行
-Give me the chance to press it at least. -No.
你去洗個澡吃點東西
You go and have bath and have food.
我來燙衣服
I will do the ironing work.
- 管好你自己的事就行了 - 我就是在找事情做啊
-Go and mind your work. -l am asking the work only.
那就去睡覺
Go and sleep.
那你可沒這運氣了 瞧瞧他在做什么
You are not lucky enough. See what he is doing!
像是送外賣出身的
He seems to have worked in the tiffin shop before.
啊 媽呀
Ouch! Mom!
他亂七八糟的動作可真多
He has enough monkey acts it looks!
我睡覺時可得警覺些
I should be alert while go for sleeping!
什么怪味
What is that strange smell?
他不會干了什么吧
Has anything happened to him?
靠 這是誰干的
Oops! Who might have done it?
神啊 告訴我這是誰干的
God! Show me the one who has done it.
出什么事了 誰在大喊大叫
What happened? Who is yelling?
我要你以后再也礙不了我的事
I will bring an end to your nuisance!
你為什么要那樣做
Why did you do that?
救救我 他要殺了我 救命啊
Save me! He is killing me. Save me.
放開他 我讓你住手
Leave him. I tell you to stop it.
現在是吵架的時候嗎
Is it the time to quarrel?
我沒和他吵架
I didn't quarrel with him.
是他用熱熨斗燙我
He pressed me with the hot iron!
看看他都做了什么
Look where he has done it!
看看 大家都看看
Look madam! All see it.
他燙錯地方了
He has pressed it in the wrong place.
下流 那種地方你怎么敢給大家看
Nasty. How dare you show the place?
我只是給大家看你燙過的褲子
I showed my trouser where you have pressed.
我什么都沒干 我那時就是睡覺來著
I didn't do anything! I was sleeping!
是他用熨斗燙我屁股
It was him who has pressed the iron on me.
- 難道你什么都沒干 - 什么都沒干
-Didn't you do anything? -Yes!
- 我讓你什么都別干 - 沒錯
-l told you not to do anything! -Yes!
- 那你為什么做這個 - 我到底做什么了
-Why did you do this then? -What did I do then?
瞧瞧他做的好事
Look, what has he done.
他還不如把褲子偷了還好些
He could've stolen it instead!
他把褲子燙了兩個大洞 這下褲子徹底廢了
He made holes in it and made it useless.
對 白癡
Yes! Idiot!
到底是哪個白癡把褲子燙穿的
Who is the idiot who has put holes in it?
我現在就要知道
I want to know it now.
- 就是你 - 我嗎
-lt's you. -Me?
我那時在睡覺 怎么可能是我
How could I do that when I was sleeping?
因為你夢游
Somnambulism!
私底下你盡管罵我
Take me to a lone place and scold me
我能接受
I will accept that.
要是你在女孩子面前讓我難堪 我從此和你一刀兩斷
If you disgrace me before the girls our friendship will get cut.
夢游是說人睡著了還會起來走動
Somnambulism is a disease which the patient walks in sleep.
- 我 - 夠了
-Me? -Enough!
-Me? -Enough, sir!
不就是條褲子嗎 吵什么吵
It is after all pants! Why all this chaos?
好我明天去學校穿什么
What will I wear in the college tomorrow?
你就沒有其他衣服褲子了嗎
Don't you have any pants and shirts with you?
這是我的制服
This is my uniform!
你又不是讀幼兒園的小孩 穿什么制服
Are you an LKG student to wear the uniform?
就是啊 你幼兒園沒讀好啊
That's it. What's the use studying big LKG studies?
神創造了我們 就是讓你用熨斗燙別人屁股的嗎
Has God created us to rub the iron in one's back?
- 別說了 - 關燈睡覺吧
-Leave it -Switch off the light and sleep.
今天開始制服問題算是
From today on wards, the uniform matter..
- 你找什么呢 - 還有個熨斗去哪里了呢
-What are you searching? -Where is the other iron box?
還有一個熨斗嗎
Another iron box!
你瞧 這里有兩個洞 可是只找到一個熨斗啊
Look! There are two holes! But the iron box is only one.
還有一個去哪里了
Where is the other one?
看看床下有沒有
Look under the bed.
這算什么 啊
What is it? Whoe!
等等 等等
Wait.
燙傷可以治愈 被言語傷害可治不了
A fire burn can be cured but not the verbal abuse
詩人Kannadasan曾經這么說
Poet Kannadasan has told it once!
是Kannadasan還是Yesudas（歌手名）
Is it Kannadasan or Yesudas (singer)?
可憐的人 他被我搞糊涂了
Poor guy! He has got confused.
你不讓我睡個好覺 她也不讓我睡個好覺
Either he or she won't allow me to sleep.
我不娶她了
Let the marriage be over.
Meera Madhu 開門
Meera! Madhu! Open the door.
怎么了 叫什么了
What happened to you? Why do you yell up?
- 快過來 - 出什么事了 - 看那里
-Come fast. -What happened to her? -Look there.
昏昏沉沉時量的尺寸難道不對嗎
Hasn't the size taken correct in sleepy mood?
好像有點大了
It is little over size!
裁縫也是這么說的
The tailor has told the same.
我可不管你是我老大還是個神經病
Whether you are my boss or a lunatic!
你哪里弄來的制服
Where did you get the uniform?
花了一整天時間定制的
It was been tailored, the whole day!
行了 行了 都準備好了嗎
Enough! Haven't you got ready yet?
- 快來 - Poongodi過來
-Come fast. -Poongodi, come here.
你沒聽到老大說的嗎
Didn't you hear the boss?
去拿點鹽來刷牙
Go and bring salt. We can clean the teeth.
你聽不懂就別亂說
Don't talk if you couldn't understand.
- 什么 - 他說的Hurry up
-What? -lt is hurry up what he said.
- Hurry up是什么意思 - 就是讓你動作快點
-What is meant by hurry up? -lt is to come fast.
站住 他叫你去哪里你就去哪里嗎
Stop there. Will you go after him if he calls you?
我告訴你 去那里 動作快點 去
I am telling now. Go this way and hurry up. Go.
Muthu Ramalingam的女兒去上大學了
Muthu Ramalingam's daughter is coming to college!
她身邊總跟著一個保鏢
She has a bodyguard with her always!
看啊 Meera 有個瞎子跟著你呢
Look there. Meera! A blind guy is coming after you.
牽住他的手 不然他要撞暀F
Hold his hand.. or else he will hit against something.
你就不能摘掉墨鏡嗎
Can you take away your glasses?
不行 那櫬人人都知道我在看著你們
Then everyone will know that I am watching!
我讓他瞧瞧我們怎擺脫他
I'll show him how can we escape from him?
Meera 我們要等你多久
Meera! How long should we wait for you?
回頭再說 先把東西給她
We can talk later. Give that to her.
在這里
Here it is.
- Allah保佑你 - 愿神保佑你
-Allah will bless you! -May God bless you!
說錯了 也愿Allah保佑你
It is not that. Same to you.
走掉了
She has gone!
- Meera呢 - 她在里頭
-Where is Meera? -She is inside.
一會就出來
She will come now.
她會去哪里呢
Where would she have gone?
- 你什么時候來的 - 你蠢呢還是笨啊
When did you come sir?
留著你自己受用 我回頭再用
Keep it all with you. I'll get it later.
我還有重要的工作
I give importance to my work.
他老是進女廁所
He goes to the ladies toilet always.
到底里面有什么
What is there in it?
糟了
Oops!
- 你站在這里干什么 快滾 - 對不起 對不起
-Why are you still here? Go away -Sorry!
多謝神靈 沒人看見我
Thank God! Nobody has seen me!
怎么停下來了
Why did you stop it?
你這也算跳舞嗎
Are you dancing?
流氓 這是個老師該做的嗎
Rogue! ls it something a master does?
你不要再出現在這個校園里
You are not supposed to come this campus any more.
快滾 滾
Get away. Go.
- 你在干什么 - 別說話
-What are you doing? -Don't talk.
難道你看不出來他碰你是出于什么目的嗎
Don't you know his intention when he touched you?
你就該狠狠揍他
You should have whacked him!
你揍他是對的
It was right when you beat him for what he did.
可是你為什么趕他走啊
Why did you send him away?
- 現在我們該怎么辦 - 女孩們 我們走
What can I do now?
動 動 動起來 青春在召喚 動起來
Youth is calling..
心靈在飛揚 動起來
The heart is flying..
你內心的閃電已醒來
Lightning in you wakes up.
舞至極點 保持極致
Till the top, keep it up.
開眼望世界 無處不美麗
Look at it.. the world is full of beauty.
你的愛能點燃火焰
The love in you will set off the fire!
在舞動中忘卻自己 感受內心的平靜
Dance forgetting you and you'll feel serene.
青春在召喚 動起來
Youth is calling..
心靈在飛揚 動起來
The heart is flying..
穿著松松垮垮的襯衫和長褲
Wear the shirt and trousers loose.
不要和壞朋友混在一起
Don't mingle with bad friends.
獲得女孩們的歡心
Get the love from the girls!
還有朋友們的支持
Be cherished with friends support
我就是河水中的魚
I am the fish in the river..
我就是樹林里的鹿
..and the deer in the forest.
我是你的戀人 望著我
I am your lover.. look at me!
換上新的服裝 舞出新的速度
New attire.. new speed!
新的戀人 讓我們享受時光
New lover! Let us enjoy.
看著像個小男孩
Looks like a small boy.
卻是個聰明的大男人
But you are a very smart guy.
女孩們都像我一樣注視著你
Girls like me eye you.
我可不傻 我可和你不一樣
I'm not a fool. I'm not the one like you.
看看我的舞步 沒有人能挑戰我
Watch my dance... nobody can challenge me.
雙腿隨著舞步扭動 和我一起舞動起來
Legs would move to your dance movements. Dance with me.
讓我們牽著手挑舞 讓我們擁抱著挑舞
Let's dance joining our hands, embrace each other..
帶著笑容
..and with a smile.
青春在召喚 動起來
Youth is calling.
心靈在飛揚 動起來
The heart is flying..
抓住她
Get her.
Madhu你和大家一起進屋子里去
Madhu! You go home with them
不關我的事
Don't do anything to me.
是Devaraj要我們干的
Devaraj is the reason for everything.
- Devaraj那混蛋在哪 - 不關我們的事啊
-Where is Devaraj? -Don't do anything to us.
我說實話 他去美國了
To tell the truth, he has gone to US.
- 他去美國了 這樣沒人會懷疑到他
-Has he gone to US? -That nobody should suspect him..
他做好了所有安排然后逃跑了
He did all arrangements and has escaped.
他不會回來了
He wouldn't come back.
只要他不回來 他就能免于一死
He will be alive till he is there.
告訴他
Tell him.
- 爸 - 你沒事吧
-Dad! -Nothing has happened to you, right?
沒事 老媽你不用擔心
No mom. You need not worry, mom.
Bhoomi當時和我們在一起
Bhoomi was there with us.
我們信任你所以把女孩們交給你保護
We sent our girl to you believing you!
就好比你的父母信任你 所以把你派到我身邊
It is like your parents has sent you to me believing you.
你不應該訴諸暴力
You should not go for any violence.
但這次都是因為我
But I myself have sent you for that.
下次再有事你盡管打電話給我
You can call me up whatever it is.
- 我會負責搞定的 - 是
-l'll take care of it. -Ok
你不能再使用暴力了
You should not go for any violence.
你要專心學習
You've to concentrate on your studies.
不光是你自己 你還要教好兩個女孩子
Not only you. You have to teach these girls too well.
- 從此以后這就是你的職責了 - 是
-lt is your duty hereafter. -OK!
我實在太困了
I feel sleepy.
明天再寫作業吧
I'll write the rest tomorrow.
- 行 去睡吧 晚安 - 天哪 終于可以去睡了
God! You all can go and sleep.
但是你們兩個明天早上4點必須在這里
You both have to be here tomorrow morning at 4.
完了 坐下吧 我們結婚后再睡吧
Good! Sit down! Let's have it after our marriage.
- 怎么了 - 我們現在就寫完作業
-What happened? -We will finish writing now itself.
讀吧
Tell us.
你沒聽見我的話嗎
Didn't you hear me?
你們寫筆記的時候都昏昏欲睡了
You fell drowsy when taking down the notes.
你看什么 去睡覺
Why do you look there? Go and sleep.
明早再繼續 走
We shall continue in the morning. Go.
終于結束了 我們也去睡覺吧
They have finished it at last. Let us go and sleep.
- 明早再繼續 - 走
-We shall continue in the morning. -Go.
我們還沒睡呢
Haven't you slept yet?
你就知道教這些多才的女孩卻忽略了我
You are teaching those learned girls, ignoring me
兩扇門都關了
All the doors have closed.
老大 他肯定生氣了 門都忘記關了
Boss! He forgot to put the lock as he was annoyed.
瞧瞧 老爸都做了什么
See what my dad has done!
我想擺脫那家伙 他卻讓他做我們的老師
When l wanted to avoid the guy he was made him our master.
他不是老師 他簡直就是班主任
He is not a master, but the head master!
以前還挺可愛 挺關心人的
He was innocent and caring at first.
現在就像個軍訓教官
Now he acts as a military officer!
他至少能對我們笑笑吧
He could smile at us a bit at least.
這樣下去不行
Hey stop!
Madhu 我們必須要他按我們的想法做事
Madhu! We should bring Bhoomi in our way.
想個辦法吧
Find a way for that.
忘了這個蠢主意 去睡一會吧
Forget this foolish act and try to get some sleep.
我們明天4點就要起床的
You have to get up at 4 in the morning.
沒人能改變他
None can change him as you think.
Bonsai說過讓女孩們通過電話愛上Bhoomi
Bonsai told before all the girls to try to love Bhoomi in the phone!
有人試過嗎 忘了愛吧
Did anyone try it? Forget love.
沒有女孩敢站在他面前
No girls have the courage to stand before him.
如果是這樣 那我自己試試呢
If so, what if I tried myself?
你為什么要試 省點勁吧
Why should you try? Don't spoil your prestige.
他不會知道是我的
He wouldn't know it is me.
他怎么可能聽不出來是你
How will you talk if he doesn't know it is you?
這個手機有隱藏呼叫者號碼的功能
This mobile restricts the caller ID.
只要用這個手機打給他 他看不到來電號碼的
If you call in this phone, the phone number will not come.
只會顯示成隱藏號碼的
It will come as the private number.
他就不知道是我了 對吧
He can't find me out, right?
他能從聲音里聽出來的
He could find you from your voice.
我能改變語調啊
I'll change my tone when I talk.
改變語調 怎么改
Another tone? How is that?
我是你的粉絲 你現在有空嗎
I am your fan!
我用這個語調他還能聽出來嗎
Can he find out with this tone?
完全聽不出 你怎么做到的
No. Not at all! How did you do it?
那就行了
That's it!
Meera 別貪玩 會出事情的
Meera! Don't play. It will pose a problem.
不會的
Nothing like that.
你也不要告訴別人
You shouldn't tell it to anyone.
隱藏號碼
What is this private number?
是誰啊
Who is it?
你聽不見我嗎
Can't you hear me talking?
是誰 我在問你 你怎么不說話啊
Who is it? I'm asking you. Won't you talk?
這個手機該仍掉了
The phone has to be in the dust bin.
- 誰 - Bhoominathan
-Who? -Bhoominathan!
- 哪個Bhoominathan - 保鏢Bhoominathan
-Which Bhoominathan? -The Bodyguard!
老大 我沒問你
I didn't ask you, boss!
我是問誰打來的電話
I asked you who was talking to you in the phone.
我問了 可是沒人回答
I too asked that but no reply.
那你就打回去問問
You could as well dial the number and ask!
看不到來電號碼
No number has come!
手機顯示不出來電號碼 怎么可能
The phone comes without a number. Is it possible?
那就去睡覺吧
Go to sleep then.
只有顯示了號碼你才能通話
You can talk only when the number appears.
真惡作劇啊
How roguish?
老大 別接
Boss! Stop.
要是對方聽見了我們的聲音卻不吱聲
If the party keeps silent even after hears our voice..
那是我們的恥辱
..it will be a shame for us.
我來說話 他怎么敢這么惡作劇
Now I will talk. How dare he is?
老大 是個女孩
Boss! It is a girl!
女孩 哪個女孩
Girl? Which girl?
問她是哪個號碼打來的
Ask her from which number is she calling!
你從哪個號碼打來的
From which number are you calling?
你要找誰
Whom do you want?
我找Bhoominathan
I want to talk to Bhoominathan?
手機是他的 聲音是我的
The phone is his... but the tone is mine.
- 你是誰啊 親愛的 - 戀人
-Who are you dear? -Lover!
你的戀人為什么要打我的手機
Why should your lover call me in my number?
是你的戀人 老大
It is your lover boss!
只有你的戀人才會打你的手機
Only your lover would call in your phone!
你是誰
Who are you?
你在耍我嗎
Are you playing with me?
我會揍你的 不要再打過來了
I'll whack you up. Keep it down.
這是椰子 這是手機啊
Is it a coconut? It is a cellular phone.
Abraham Lincoln辛辛苦苦才發明出來的
Abraham Lincoln would have toiled much to invent that!
到底是Abraham Lincoln還是Abdul Kalam
（印度某任總統 同是也是著名科學家）
Was it Abraham Lincoln or Abdul Kalam?
他又被搞糊涂了
He himself has got confused.
我們早上可以問問他
We will ask him in the morning!
這辦法肯定起作用了
The idea has been worked out!
今天足夠了
It's enough for him
明天再繼續
The rest can be tomorrow.
開開門
Open the door.
你們準備好下樓來
You both get ready and come downstairs.
- 起床了 - Meera起床了
-Get up! -Meera, get ready!
- 快點 - 見鬼了
-Fast. -Damn it.
Meera快點準備好下樓去
Meera! Get ready fast and come.
要不班主任又要上來了
Or the head master would come up.
接吧 你掛斷他還會再打來的
Attend it. If you cut it he would call you again!
像是打錯了 不用接
This look like a phony number. No need to attend it.
- 瞧瞧 - 你可以關機的
-See! -You could switch it off.
主人說過手機不能關機
Sir has told that the phone shouldn't be switched off.
- 別多嘴 - 掛掉了
-Keep quiet. -lt has got cut.
你干嘛老是說這一句啊
Why do you tell it again and again?
下課 我有重要的事情 你們快走
I have do urgent work. Go fast.
你
You...
你又掛了嗎
Have you disconnected it?
你掛了算你聰明
You are safe as you have cut it.
要是被我逮住了 我要殺了你
If you are caught I would kill you.
別說了
Keep quiet.
終于可以睡個安穩覺了
I can sleep peacefully now.
Meera起來洗漱啦
Meera! Get up and get ready.
干嘛這么早叫我啊
Why do you wake me up so early?
侈知道現在幾點了
Do you know what the time is?
保鏢7點就穿好制服了
The bodyguard has got ready with his uniform at 7.
該死的制服 我一定要做些什么
Damn uniform! I'll have to do something for that.
Parvathi Nambiyar 我看出來了 這是英文
Parvathi Nambiyar! I've picked up English.
老大 是個Parvathi Nambiyar打給你的
Boss! A Parvathi Nambiyar calls you.
- 又是你 - 這個Parvathi Nambiyar是誰啊
-ls it you? -Who is that Parvathi Nambiyar?
不是Parvathi Nambiyar 是隱藏號碼
（隱藏號碼的英文是Private Number 音似Parvathi Nambiyar）
It is not Parvathi Nambiyar. It is private number!
拼寫不是一樣的嗎
Is the spelling same for both?
就是她 你終于又打來了 我等你到現在了
It is her. You have come! I was expecting you till now.
你還沒接起來呢
You haven't switched it on.
不接聽你沒法通話的
You could talk only if you switch it on.
- 你可以走了 - 你明白了就好
-You can go. -lf you have understood, it is good.
- 你這混蛋 - 你叫我嗎 老大 - 原來在和那女孩說話
Have you called me boss? It's the girl.
不要只在電話里說 有種當面說
Don't talk in the phone. Come in person!
我會治好你這瘋子的
I will cure your insanity!
沒法治的
It can't be cured.
- 我是因你而瘋狂 - 啥
-l am crazy after you! -What?
我非常喜歡你穿的制服 還有你戴的帽子 墨鏡 還有你的一舉一動
I like very much the uniform you wear, cap, glasses, your walk and style!
- 你是我的英雄 - 英雄 誰的英雄 什么英雄
-You are my hero! -Hero? Whose hero.. what hero?
我不是為了你穿這身制服的
I didn't wear this uniform for you!
你這么個神經病打電話來
When a mad person like you calls me up..
說什么喜歡我
..and tells me that you like me..
難道你還指望我來追求你
..do you expect me to come after you?
你要是再打給我 我不但要砸你的手機 還要打你的人
If you call me again, you will lose your phone and get hurt
可是你要先知道我是誰
You have to know who I am.
我管你是誰 我照打不誤 別再打來了 神經病
Whatever it is.. You'll get hurt in any case. Keep the phone down.
- 神馬情況 如果他還穿制服的話
-What happened? -lt will show he respects my call..
就證明他在乎我的話
..if he wears the uniform again!
如果他換下制服了 就證明他在意我的話
If he changes his uniform it'll show he responds to my call
- 大叔 - 啥事
-Uncle! -What is it?
保鏢今天沒穿制服
Bodyguard hasn't wore the uniform.
沒穿制服 你怎么知道的
Didn't he wear? How do you know it?
- 我從窗戶里偷窺到的 偷窺到的
-l peeped through the window. -Did you see!
簡直太帥了
It was very superb!
你看了不該看的 還要講給你的未婚夫聽
You saw the nasty scene and tells that now to the would be.
- 我要 - 你這個蠢大叔
-l will.... -You foolish uncle!
- 他穿著花襯衫呢 - 花襯衫
-He is wearing the color dress. -Colour dress?
誰讓他穿的
Who did he ask to wear it?
你還看
Why do you look there again?
這亂七八糟的衣服是什么啊
What is this nasty dress?
- 他看上去帥極了 - 笨蛋 別胡扯了
-He looks very superb! -Stupid! ..stop blabbering.
Bhoomi你穿新襯衫做什么
Bhoomi! Why are you in this new dress?
今天是你生日嗎
Is it your birthday?
以后我都會這么穿
It will be like this, henceforth.
生活里應該有些改變
There should be some change in life!
- 我不喜歡這種改變 - 我還不喜歡你呢
-l didn't like this change! -l too don't like you!
他的話多傷人啊
How bad was his word?
我們的療法起作用了
Our treatment has worked out well.
那以前憎恨女人的人
The one who hated the women before..
如今盯著女孩們看呢
..is now watching them very well!
別看了 快走
Don't look! Come.
你可真好
You are very kind
看保鏢的衣服
Look at the dress of the bodyguard.
你換了衣服看上去很時尚啊
You have changed the uniform and have come stylish!
是不是去相親了啊
Have you gone for your engagement?
沒錯 我在找一個女孩
Yes! I'm looking out for a girl!
要是被我找到了 我會好好照顧她的
If I get her, I'll see to her.
-這樣可以吧 - 可以
-ls it okay with you? -lt's okay
如果他知道是我們 我們就死定了
If he knew that we are those we will be finished.
膽小鬼 你這樣會暴露我們的
Coward! It looks like you will show us to him!
鎮定地走
Come quietly.
你個鬼啊
Why do you laugh?
站住 你再說一遍 再說一遍
Stop! Tell it again! Tell it again!
再溫柔點
Once again softly.
再輕一點 你走吧
Tell it quietly. You can go.
他來了
He is coming.
你是誰 你在哪里
Who are you! Where are you?
我就在這里 你在哪里
I am here only. Where are you?
說哈咯
Tell hello.
電話里說哈咯
Tell it in the phone.
沒事 這里有個
It is nothing. It is here...
我問你呢 你在哪里
I am asking you. Where are you now?
你剛和一個女孩拌嘴
You have quarreled with a girl.
我那時和你擦肩而過
I crossed you only then!
我今天一定有辦法找到你
I will find a solution for you today.
你繼續說啊 不要停
You talk... and keep talking.
我25分鐘內就能找到你
I'll find you in 25 minutes!
何必如此麻煩呢
Why do you bother much?
說你愛我
Tell me that you love me!
我馬上就會出現在你眼前
I'll be before you the next moment.
帶著美麗的笑容 - 笑容
-..with a stylish smile! -Smile?
你嘴里一顆牙都不會剩下
There won't be a tooth left in your mouth.
你不是要愛情嗎
Do you want love?
那就不是一刻鐘的問題了
Not only 25 minutes.
你一輩子都找不到我
You will have to search for me for your life.
你打我一輩子電話我都不會愛上你
I will not love you if you call me the entire life.
你說你喜歡我的那個時候
The moment I threw it away when you told me..
我就把手機扔了 知道嗎
..that you like me... know it?
你今天穿襯衫很帥啊
You look handsome in this dress!
但是你要把它塞進褲子里
But you have to tuck in the shirt.
你的發型就像Gemini Ganesh（印度著名演員 2005年逝世）
Your hair style is like Gemini Ganesh.
你要用手重新整理一下你的頭發
You have to undo the hair and redo it with the hand.
那才是如今流行的發型
That's the latest trend.
我會塞襯衫理頭發的
I will tuck my shirt and do the hair.
不用你來操心
You don't have to worry for that.
你有種就告訴我你是誰
Tell your name if you have courage.
你要名字干什么
Why do you need the name?
你就叫我Ammukutty好了
You can call me Ammukutty as well.
- 什么 - Ammukutty
-What? -Ammukutty!
Ammukutty!
Ammukutty
哈咯 你是Ammukutty
Hello! Are you Ammukutty?
你今天穿襯衫很帥啊
You look handsome in this dress!
但是你要把它塞進褲子里
But you have to tuck in the shirt.
你要用手重新整理一下你的頭發
You have to undo the hair and re do it with the hand.
沙漠里也開始下小雨了
It has started to drizzle in the desert.
慢慢地就會變成大雨
Then, it'll be heavy rain
是誰啊 是誰啊
Who is it? Who is it?..
是誰折磨我的心靈
The one who tortures my mind.
又是誰閉眼在盲行
The one who closes the eyes and going!
是誰啊 是誰啊
Who is it? Who is it?..
是誰和我若即又若離
The one who stayed close to me. The one who stayed away from me.
問題就是答案 就像分居不可相見的情侶
The answer came as the question! As the separation who stayed away.
是誰啊 是誰啊
Who is it? Who is it?..
字
字幕
字幕調
字幕調效
字幕調效：
字幕調效：l
字幕調效：la
字幕調效：lai
字幕調效：laix
字幕調效：laixy
噢喲
Oh God!
字
字幕
字幕調
字幕調效
字幕調效：
字幕調效：l
字幕調效：la
字幕調效：lai
字幕調效：laix
字幕調效：laixy
無論清晨還是深夜 我的心中總充滿著爭斗
A tussle goes on in me in the morning and evening.
噢 媽啊
Oh mom!
即使熟睡時 夢中也在上演古典舞劇
Kathakali (Classic dance) in my mind goes on when I sleep.
無論清晨還是深夜 我的心中總充滿著爭斗
A tussle goes on in me in the morning and evening.
即使熟睡時 夢中也在上演古典舞劇
Kathakali in my mind goes on when I sleep.
她無時無刻不占據著我的頭腦
She is in me in the day, in the night and in my mind
無論在夢中還是在現實 她就像影子緊緊追隨著我
She is in my dream and in reality like a shadow!
我的心四處搜尋她
My heart searches for her everywhere.
是誰啊 是誰啊
Who is it? Who is it?..
她像龍 從天而降至我的頭上
She gets down on the top of my head like a dragon!
然后開始折磨我
After getting down in me she starts torturing me.
萬人之中難以尋覓她的蹤跡
She makes it impossible to find her out among others.
卻唯有她的面容最有魅力
Her face is more attractive than others!
她給我的愛無形無色
She makes love to me being invisible!
是誰啊 是誰啊
Who is it? Who is it?..
是誰折磨我的心靈
The one who tortures my mind.
又是誰閉眼在盲行
The one who closes the eyes and going!
是誰啊 是誰啊
Who is it? Who is it?..
是誰和我若即
The one who stayed close to me.
又是誰和我若離
The one who stayed away from me.
問題就是答案
The answer came as the question!
就像分居不可相見的情侶
As the separation..
好吧 我找不到你
Ok, I couldn't find you out.
行了告訴我吧 你的真名是什么
Ok tell me now. What is your original name?
- Ammukutty - 你撒謊
-Ammukutty! -You are lying
好吧 那告訴我你是哪個班的總行吧
Ok tell me in which class you are studying?
至少告訴我 你是哪個專業的吧
At least you can tell me which department.
為什么要告訴你 讓你找到我罵我一頓嗎
Why? To find me out and scold, right?
不是 不是 我現在已經不生你的氣了
No, Now I am not angry with you
那你是開始喜歡上我了
Then, have you started to love me?
是這樣
It is..
沒見過你怎么可能喜歡上你
How can I love without seeing you in person?
你能見我但是有個條件
You can see
你不能再總是跟著那女孩子了
You've to stop going behind that girl
跟著那個女孩子 你是說
Behind the girl? What do you mean?
跟著Meera
Behind Meera?
我不喜歡看你整天像根尾巴一樣跟著她
I don't like you roaming behind her like a tail
她覺得她自己是誰啊
What is she thinking herself?
世界小姐啊
Is she the Miss World?
她為什么總是小題大作 你這么優秀 她卻讓你做她的跟班
Why does she overact making you being a gem of a person roaming behind her?
住嘴
Stop it
你有什么資格對Meera說三道四的
Who are you to talk nonsense about our Meera?
夠了 我不想知道你的底細了
It's enough. I don't need to know your whereabouts and details
不要再打電話給我了 消失吧
Don't call me again
我說了不要再打過來了
I told you not to call me again.
你怎么又打過來了
Then why did you call me?
- 快掛掉 - 別掛掉
-Cut the call -Don't cut it.
我以后再也不會說Meera的壞話了
Henceforth l won't talk anything wrong about Meera
那是因為她沒有哪點不好的
You can't find anything wrong about her
我想聽聽你說說Meera的事
When you talk about Meera I wish to know more about her.
你能說給我聽嗎
Will you tell me?
你知道了又怎么樣
What will you do by knowing that?
因為那樣我就能向她學習了 你就會喜歡我了
If I behave like her, you will like me. That's why
你怎才不說話
Why have you become silent?
這不是后天能學來的
It is not money to earn
那是她與生俱來的品質
It is character It should come by birth
就說一點
Just know one thing
你見過哪個老板的女兒
Have you ever seen a boss daughter..
能和自己的服裝廠女工們打成一片的呢
..who mingle closely with their garments company workers?
只有Semmanooru Muthuramaiah的女兒
It is Semmanooru Muthuramaiah's daughter..
我們的Meera
..our Meera
以前我們老板總是陷入麻煩
Once upon a time our sir always entered into troubles..
是我們的Meera改變了他 讓他成了人人贊揚的人
..but our Meera changed him and made him to be praised by people
以前我是個混混 只懂用暴力去獲得東西
Earlier I too have thought to attain anything by force and roamed as a rogue.
是我們的Meera讓我明白了
But our Meera made me to understand that..
靠暴力是統治不了國家的 暴力只能統治森林
..strength is not suitable to rule the nation and it is suitable to the forest
我們要用愛去統治一切
..and you've to rule everything by the love
保護Muthuramaiah是我的責任
It is my duty coming as escort for Muthuramaiah
但保護Meera是我的榮耀
Now I feel as a honor to be a protector to Meera
你說Meera的不是 我就不高興
I got angry when you told nonsense about Meera
所以我才責怪你 我很抱歉 非常抱歉
That's why I scolded you
你為什么說抱歉
Why do you say sorry?
做錯了事的人是我
It is me who has done the mistake
現大我徹底明白了
Now I've understood clearly
不是明白她 而是明白你了 Bhoomi我愛你
Not about her ...about you
Bhoomi你想親眼見見我嗎
Bhoomi! Do you want to see me in person?
- 我當然想 - 那你出來吧
-Yes I want to -Then, come out
我在花園里呢
I am in the garden
- 往前走 - 你在哪呢
-Come forward -Where are you?
就在這里
Here only
我就站在樹下 你看到了嗎
Can't you see that I am standing under the tree?
嗨 別動了 就站在那里
Hey, stop Stop there
我過來找你
I'll come close to you
閉上眼睛就站在那里
Close your eyes and stay there
我讓你睜眼再睜眼
Open your eyes after I tell you
- 那快過來吧 - 急什么啊
-Come fast -Why are you in hurry?
我來了
I am coming close to you
現在睜眼吧
Now open your eyes
你毀了我的好夢
You've spoiled everything
我有叫你端茶來嗎
Did I ask you for tea at this time?
老大 那是Poongodi啊
That's Poongodi, boss
她做事情盡心盡責
Because she did her duty correct..
所以主人讓她懷孕了
..sir made her pregnant in that house
什么 懷孕了
What? Pregnant?
哎呀 不是懷孕 是永久留用
（懷孕pregnant和永久留用permanent讀音相似）
Oh God! It is not pregnant it is permanent
- 懷孕是指有喜了 - 有喜了
-Pregnant means carrying -Carrying?
好了 走吧
Ok, go
我當著他的面說這個做什么
Why did you tell this before him?
你可以回頭和我單獨說啊
You could have told it to me later
- 我總是被英語羞辱 - 不提了
-Because of this English I have felt ashamed often -Leave it.
- 嗨 Amavasai - 什么事 老大
-Hey Amavasai! -What boss?
- 我剛才夢見她了 - 什么
-Today she came in my dream -What?
你夢見我的Poongodi了
Did my Poongodi come in your dream?
你都和我訂婚了 你還進別人的夢里
Having engagement with me, are you coming in others' dreams?
不是她 我夢見的是Ammukutty
Not her. lt is Ammukutty!
原來是Ammukutty 嚇死我了
Ammukutty! I felt scared
那你見到Ammukutty了
Have you seen Ammukutty?
你的Poongodi讓我連她的臉都沒見到
Your Poongodi didn't allow me to see her face
她來的真是時候 把我吵醒了
She came at the right time and woke me up
把你吵醒了 好你之前是在睡覺嘍
Did she wake you up? Then, were you in sleep?
那我就不明白了 她進來的時候你怎么不自己醒過來呢
What is this boss? Why didn't you wake up when she was coming here?
- 你個白癡 睡著了才能做夢 - 不是的
-Dreams will come in sleep, you idiot! -Not like that
你有心就能做白日夢
Dreams should come when you are in sense
Bharthiyaar說這就叫真愛
Bharthiyaar said it is called true love
是Bharthiyaar說的還是Bharathi Raja
Was it Bharthiyaar or Bharathi Raja?
真可憐 他又糊涂了
So pity! He got confused
我和你說
I'll tell you one thing
愛情和婚姻就像旅途
Love and marriage are like journey
愛情就像坐長途車旅行
Love is like bus journey
你覺得不滿意 你可以隨時下車
If we don't like, we can get down in the way.
婚姻就像坐飛機旅行
Marriage is like air plane journey
你覺得不滿意 你沒法半路跳下去
If we don't like it, we can't get down in the middle
你會摔死的
We'll die
走開 什么亂七八糟的
Go away. Nonsense!
保鏢呢
Where is the bodyguard?
他去女生宿舍了
He has gone to ladies hostel
AMMUKUTTY
Ammukutty
Why are you standing here like in the airport?
你舉個牌子站在這里做什么 這里又不是機場
Nothing boss, seeing this name they will come here.
沒事的 老大 她們看見名字就會過來的 所以我才舉著這塊牌子
That's why this setup
- 老大 - 什么爛主意
-Boss! -Damn your idea!
牌牌爛了
The board has broken
老大 為什么啊 你為什么把Ammukutty撕爛了啊
Why boss? Why did you tear Ammukutty?
- Ammukutty不是她的真名 - 啊 不會吧
-Ammukutty is not her real name -Oh god!
那我們怎么能把她找出來呢
Then how can we find out that girl?
她現在會打電話給我的
She'll call me now
我和她電話里不停地聊
I'll keep chatting with her
同時你溜進女生宿舍
Meanwhile you enter into the hostel and..
要是看到哪個女生在打電話 你就拍張照片帶回來
..if any girl is talking in the phone you take her photo and come back
那個女生就是Ammukutty
She will be Ammukutty
- 老大 手機響了 - 是她 是她
-Boss! Phone is ringing -lt is her
是她 那你問她
Is it her? Then while you are talking with her..
她住哪間房間 把房號告訴我
..ask her in which room she is in and tell me
我會請求她的允許 然后拍張照片帶給你
I'll take her photo with her permission
好吧 我懂你的感覺
I know your feeling
那這樣吧
Then do one thing
你叫她出來
While you are talking with her, make her to come out
我偷偷給她拍照片 保證不讓她知道
I'll take her photo without her knowledge
哦喲 這也行不通
Oh god! This too didn't work out
你去哪里 往后面走
Where do you go? Go backside
一大清早的 你在我們宿舍門口干什么呢
At morning what are you doing before our hostel?
你就住在這棟里嗎 我想像不出來
Are you staying in this hostel? I couldn't imagine.
你的房間號是什么
What is your room number?
你是要我的房間號呢還是手機號
Do you want my room number or my phone number?
不要告訴我
No need to tell
我自己能找到
I myself will find it out
除了謹遵命令外
would do what I was told
我別無他念
I don't know other than that
怎么能馬上就見面呢
How can it possible to meet at once?
我會告訴你什么時候見面的
I'll tell you the time to our meeting
你不想告訴他 那我去告訴他
You don't want to tell I'll go and tell him
我可見到你了 是吧
I've seen you, isn't it?
聽我說
Try to listen to me!
我和你說今天不可能
I am telling you that today is not possible
她背對著我
She is showing her back to me
我到她面前去 拍她的臉
I'll go before her and take a photo of her face
- 你是誰 - 你在做什么
-Who is it? -What are you doing?
- 我什么都沒做 - 你在做什么
-l am not doing anything -What are you doing?
她用英語說什么來著
What is she saying in English?
也許就是她
May be she is that girl
我給她也拍一張照吧
I'll take her photo too
- 謝天謝地 這里沒有人 - 你來這里干什么
-Thank god! No one is here -Why did you come here?
我和你說了多少次了 不要到這里來
How many times should I tell you not to come here?
這是神馬情況 所有人都在打手機啊
What is this? Whole gang is speaking in the cell phone
我糊涂了
I am confused
不能糊涂啊
No confusion
我給所有人都拍張照帶回去給他看
I'll take all of these girls photos and show him
讓他自己選
Let him pick it her up
- 你是誰 - 那是誰
-Who are you? -Who is that?
- 抓小偷啊 - 小偷 - 大家快來
-Thief! -Thief? -Come fast
為什么小偷這時候出現啊
Why did he come at this moment?
我的事情本來就多了
They are giving me a lot of work.
- 小偷在哪里 大姐 - 女孩們快來抓小偷啊
-Where is he madam? -Come girls, let's catch the thief
- 抓的就是你 - 大姐 你為啥打我啊
-You -Madam, why are you hitting me?
偷拍女孩還不夠 你還想親我
Not only taking the girls photos Do you want to kiss me?
女孩們 把他打出去
Girls, bash him off
慢點 慢點 把我扔地上了
Slowly! Slowly! Don't throw me down
慢點啊
Take me slowly
那邊吵什么呢
Is there any struggle?
好像是個瘋子從樓上摔下來了
I think some mad guy has fallen down from the building
大家正抬他去醫院呢
They are taking him to the hospital
- 好吧 那我晚上再打給你 - 別掛
-Ok, l'll call you in the evening -Don't cut the call
- 你繼續說 - 他還挺咋呼
-You go ahead -He is busy.
喊什么喊 再喊把他舌頭割掉
Is he shouting? Cut his tongue
是 是 是
Yes!
啊 那個抬過去的是我的搭檔
Is it my party going there?
你晚上再打給我吧
You call me in the evening
把尸體還給我
Give me the body!
慢點 慢點 媽啊
Slowly! Oh mom!
不要亂拉
Don't pull me as you wish!
我的身體都要散架了
My parts could break up
我們在哪里
Where we are now?
公共廁所
In the toilet?
- 在別墅 - 別墅
-ln the house -House!
就算上了車我也記得廁所的味道
After coming in the auto it still is in my mind.
- 啊呀 大叔 - 沒錯 是我 - 怎么回事
-Oh gosh! Uncle! -Yes, it is me -What is this?
- 發生什么了 - 沒什么 - 沒什么
-How has it happened? -Nothing -Nothing?
他就是摔了一跤
He has just fallen down
- 他在哪里摔的啊 - 你就明明白白告訴她 我是被打的
-Where has he fallen down? -Tell her clearly that l was beaten
被打了 那你沒跪下求饒嗎
Beaten? Then didn't you fall down?
我跪下了 叫他們別打我
I fell down at everyone's feet telling not to hit me
可我一跪下 所有人都拿腳踹我
When l fell down at their feet they stamped me
多少人踹你
How many people?
我被踹的時候怎么數人頭
How could I count them when I was getting beats?
她們打我的嘴 我還怎么數數
How could I count when they hit in my mouth?
其中有個胖女人 好像練過空手道
Among them, one fat lady looks like learnt Karate
她扇耳光的手法與眾不同
Her slaps are different from others
她踢我的時候我的蛋蛋都被踢到喉嚨口了
When she kicked me with her leg, my balls came to here
- 閉嘴 - 我當然閉嘴了
-Shut up your mouth -Then l closed my mouth..
否則蛋蛋就從嘴里掉出來了
..else it would've come out
后來我辛辛苦苦才把各個器官復位
After that, I have toiled much to get the things in it's own place
- 只有造物主才能明白我的痛楚- 你怎么會傷成這樣
-Only my creator knew my pain -Why did you get hurt like this?
難道我是花錢讓人來揍我的嗎
Did I get it by giving money?
我說不要打了 她們還是把我打得青一塊紫一塊
When l said no, they hit me black and blue
當時你在哪里
Where were you in that situation?
我接到一個重要的電話 所以
I received an important call. That's why..
就是因為這個電話才會發生這一切
Because of that phone call this has happened
老大 你撐著
Boss! You be brave
我死之前一定會幫你搞得水落石出
I'll find out your problem before l die.
爸 你來了
Come dad!
- 主人 你什么時候到的 - 我在這里有個會議
-Sir! When did you come? -l had a meeting here
順便過來看看Meera
On the way l came to see Meera
Bhoomi 學校什么時候放假
Bhoomi! When will your college close down?
下個月25號
Next month 25th
- 放假后就回家 - 好
-You come to our house the next day -Ok
大家都在等Meera考完試
All are waiting for Meera's exam
等她考完試 她得去倫敦
After her exams, she has to go to London
我們已經決定在倫敦給她辦婚禮
We've decided to conduct her marriage there
你為什么一個人坐在這里
Why are you sitting here alone?
沒什么 就是坐著
Nothing. Just sitting
來吧 我們進屋去
Come, let's go in the room
沒事 我們就在這里坐一會兒
It's ok, let's sit down here for a while
坐吧
Sit down!
有些事情我一直想和你說
I was thinking to tell you something for a long time
說吧 盡管說吧
Tell me. Tell me whatever it is
你為什么沒帶手機 你爸爸等你接電話
Why did you keep your phone there? Dad is on the line
快來
Come fast!
你爸爸沒有打你電話 我騙你的
Dad didn't call you I lied you
這個時候你一個人在和Bhoomi說什么
Why are you talking alone with Bhoomi at this time?
我 我沒說什么
That is.. just nothing
看到你現在樣子我很害怕
By seeing your behaviour I feel scared
你都已經是訂了婚的人了
Already your engagement is over
可是上天有不同的安排
But God's decision is different
否則Bhoomi也不會進入我的生活
Else Bhoomi wouldn't have entered into my life
你知道的 他不愛你 Meera
As you think he is not loving you Meera
我現在不是Meera
Now I am not Meera
只要能做他的戀人就足夠了
It's enough for me if I live as his lover
我不能離開他
I can't be without him
要是你父親知道了怎么辦
What if your father knows this?
要是Bhoomi知道了這一切
If Bhoomi knows about this,
你覺得他會為了你帶你走而和你父親決裂鬧翻嗎
..do you think that he'll fight for you with your dad and take you?
你還是不懂他
You haven't understood him clearly
他對你父親那么忠誠 他不會背叛你父親的
Because he is having faith on your father he can't betray your father
如果他知道你就是那個電話里的女孩
If he knows that you are he girl talking on the phone..
他不會接受的
..he won't accept you
他會把你交給你父母 然后獨自離開
He'll handover you to your parents and go his way
一定會這樣的
This is what is going to happen.
Kamaraj說如果瓦片破了 我們可以換一片
Kamaraj said before that if a tile breaks, we can change it..
可是如果心智破了就沒法換了
..but we can't change if mind break.
是Kamaraj說的還是Suruli Rajan說的
Kamaraj or Suruli Rajan?
真可憐 他又糊涂了
So pity! He got confused
拿好這片瓦
Take that tile.
他正在幫我做工 可是又被我搞糊涂了
He is doing his duty but l have confused him.
拿好了
Hold it strong.
- 別因為嫌我煩我就走開 - 行 行
-Don't leave me and go annoyed. -Ok.
跑啊 跑啊（泰米爾語中跑是ootu 瓦也是ootu 讀音完全一樣）
Run, run (Tile)
哦喲哇
Oh God!
誰啊
Who?
媽啊
Oh God!
你怎么沒打電話給我
Why don't you call me?
是不是起床晚了
Did you wake up late?
我一直都沒睡著 又怎么起床呢
First I have to sleep for that. Isn't it?
我也是
Me too.
我一直在凌晨才睡著 夢見你了
I had a dream about you in the dawn.
我在你夢時長什么樣
How was I looking in your dream?
誰知道啊
Who knows that?
好你不需要在夢里見我了
Hence you don't need to see me in your dream.
我來見你
I'll meet you.
你騙我
It is a lie.
不 我說真的
No, I'll come.
- 真的 - 你為什么懷疑我
-Really? -Why do you suspect me?
我說我會來見你的
I am telling that I will come.
那告訴我你現在在哪里 我馬上就來
Tell me. Where are you now? I will come immediately.
哦 現在不行
Oh! Not now.
下星期天在植物園見面好不好
Will you come on next Sunday at the botanical garden?
等一下
One minute.
就等一下
Wait for a minute.
他朝這里來了
He is coming here.
下星期天你們有什么安排嗎
Do you have any program on next Sunday?
我們哪里都不去 怎么了
We don't go anywhere. Why?
我要出去一下 所以問問
I have to go one place. That's why.
- 去哪里 - 去見醫生
-Where? -To meet a doctor.
如果你有安排 我就不去了
If you have any program I won't go.
我和醫生取消預約好了
I will cancel meeting the doctor!
沒事 你星期天盡管去吧
No, you can go on Sunday.
星期天我有空
Sunday I am free.
你什么時候到
What time will you come there?
下午3點整
Evening at 3'o clock.
那我2:45就到
I'll come there at 2.45pm
你還沒告訴我你的真名呢
You didn't say your real name.
我們就要見面了 然后呢
We are going to meet each other. Then what?
好 那就星期天3點
Ok. We will meet on Sunday at 3'o clock.
雨點的節奏 火車的節奏 心跳的節奏 都是有韻律的節奏
Rhythmic heart beats are same as the rain and train
帶來些許欣慰也帶來些許苦惱
Little comfort and little pain.
雨點的節奏 火車的節奏 心跳的節奏 都是有韻律的節奏
Rhythmic heart beats are same as the rain and train
帶來些許欣慰也帶來些許苦惱
Little comfort and little pain.
她會準時出現 還是讓我久候
Will she come fast or make me wait?
她會秋波凝視還是微笑誘惑
Will she stare at me or give her seductive smile?
她是被動吻我還是主動擁抱
Will she kiss me only if asked or hug me on her own?
她會和我合體然后殺了我
Will she make love with me and kill me?
雨點的節奏 火車的節奏 心跳的節奏 都是有韻律的節奏
Rhythmic heart beats are same as the rain and train
帶來些許欣慰也帶來些許苦惱
Little comfort and little pain.
我的頭腦已經失去控制 自動想你
My mind thinks about you without any control.
我的頭腦已經失去束縛 自動舞蹈
..and it dances with joy!
無需語言告訴我 泰米爾語言充滿魔力
Without any language to tell me Tamil words are becharming.
在愛的街道 我的欲望無邊無界
My desire is boundless in the love street.
在愛的回憶 你的影子悄然出現
In the memories, the shadow gets burst.
征服了我的是你的聲音
You got into me with your voice!
殺死了我的是你的回憶 殺手就是你
Your memories kills me you killer!
雨點的節奏 火車的節奏 心跳的節奏 都是有韻律的節奏
Rhythmic heart beats are same as the rain and train
帶來些許欣慰也帶來些許苦惱
Little comfort and little pain.
河水困在螺殼
The water of river Ganges caught up in the conch..
渴望去到對岸
..and craves to go to other shore.
男孩困在美夢 終夜無法入眠
A small child by keeping a dream is without a sleep.
你就快出現在我面前
You have to come before me soon.
請在夢中現身 直到見面那一天
Show me your face in my dream till you come before me.
連秒種都走得那么緩慢
The arrows in the clock which go slow..
想見你的心卻那么急促
..are hurrying me up to see you!
雨點的節奏 火車的節奏 心跳的節奏 都是有韻律的節奏
Rhythmic heart beats are same as the rain and train
帶來些許欣慰也帶來些許苦惱
Little comfort and little pain.
雨點的節奏 火車的節奏 心跳的節奏 都是有韻律的節奏
Rhythmic heart beats are same as the rain and train
帶來些許欣慰也帶來些許苦惱
Little comfort and little pain.
她會準時出現 還是讓我久候
Will she come fast or make me wait?
她會秋波凝視還是微笑誘惑
Will she stare at me or give her seductive smile?
她是被動吻我還是主動擁抱
Will she kiss me only if asked or hug me on her own?
她會和我合體然后殺了我
Will she make love with me and kill me?
我們要出門了 快開門
We have to go out. Open the door.
不會吧
Oh God!
準備好就出來 我們等你
Get ready and come. We will be waiting.
等等 我要去見醫生的
Wait. I want to meet a doctor.
那天你說你沒安排
I fixed the appointment today because you said on that day
我才預約在今天
..that you have no program today.
我忘了
I forgot that.
那我們和你一起去吧
We will also come with you.
我們也去看醫生 走吧
We will meet the doctor and go.
不行 醫生說只能一個人去
No, doctor told that I have come alone.
那你一個進去
You go alone.
我們在診室外面等你
We will stand outside the consulting room.
- 醫生不會同意的 - 為什么呢
-Doctor will not accept it. -Why?
因為這個醫生沒有診室
Because doctor have no consulting room.
這算哪門子醫生
Which doctor is that?
這下我更想去見見這個醫生了
That means I want to meet that doctor.
他叫什么名字
What is his name?
他沒什么名氣 說出來你也不知道
He is not a big doctor to tell his name.
我們就叫他醫生 醫生的
We will call as doctor.
你盡撒謊
Everything you tell are lies.
說實話 你要去哪里
Tell the truth. Where are you going?
我想去見個朋友
I want to meet a friend..
那你干嘛要對我隱瞞呢
Why are you hiding it from me?
因為那位朋友是女孩
My friend is a girl.
- 女孩 - 是的
-Girl? -Yes!
她也在我們學校讀書
She is studying in our college.
她經常打電話給我
She has called me often.
她說她今天會和我見面
She said that she will meet me today.
你愛上她了嗎
Do you love her?
- 我喜歡她 - 喜歡她
-l like her. -For her?
她漂亮嗎
Is she looking beautiful?
我還沒見過她
I haven't seen her.
- 你還沒見過她嗎 - 不過她見過我
-Didn't you see her? -But she has seen me.
今天我要去求婚
Today I am going to arrange marriage proposal.
今天我要去見她
I am going to see her.
如果她不漂亮呢
If she doesn't look beautiful when you see her in person?
漂亮不漂亮都是騙眼睛的 騙不了我們的心
Beauty is only for our eyes. Not for our mind.
難道我看見了她 我心里的愛就會消失
When l see her will my love in my mind vanish?
好吧 你早就該說了 不是嗎
Ok, you could have told it before
你還浪費什么時間呢
Why are you wasting the time?
快去準備吧
Get ready soon.
我準備好就來
I'll get ready and come.
你即然提到她了 我也想見見她
I want to see her when you said about her.
我能和你一起去嗎
Shall I come with you?
啊 不行
Oh! No!
你和我一起去 她看見了會不高興的
If you come with me she won't like that.
因為我一直跟著你 她已經和我吵過一次了
Already she had a fight with me that I am following you.
我不會讓她看見我的
She can't see me.
我會躲起來偷偷看她
I'll hide and see her.
- 真有這個必要嗎 - 有啊 我想見見她
-ls all this necessary? -Yes, I want to see her.
聽著
Please listen to me.
你就站在這里
You be stand here.
你從這里能看到我們兩個人
You can see both of us from here.
時間過得好慢
Time is not moving.
還有半個小時
There is half an hour to go.
你能幫我個忙嗎
Will you do a help for me?
說吧
Tell me.
現在你就是Ammu
Now you are Ammu.
你把自己想成是Ammu就是行了
You just think like that.
我待會要和她說的話 我先和你練習一遍
I'll just practice with you what l am going to say her.
行嗎
Ok?
你來了
Have you come?
我真不敢相信
I couldn't believe it.
這么多天你都不見我 為什么你要這么做
These days you didn't meet me.. and why did you do like this?
你是真的愛我嗎 還是和我開玩笑的
Do you love me truly? Or are you kidding me?
那天你在電話里說愛我
That day I couldn't say anything to you..
我什么都沒說
..when you proposed me through the phone.
但現在我要當面說出來 我也愛你 非常地愛你
But now I am telling you in person.
這樣說可以嗎
Is this ok to speak like this?
現在我有信心了
Now I am confident.
- 你怎么不祝我好運呢 - 祝你好運
Why don't you say all the best?
你來了嗎
Have you come?
你在哪里
Where are you?
你看見我了嗎
Did you see me?
我不想見你了
I don't want to see you.
以后你也見不到我了
Hence forth you won't see me.
我和你說過不能讓Meera來
Though I have told you that Meera shouldn't come..
可你還是把她帶來了 還碰她的肩膀
..you touched her shoulder and brought here.
Ammu 我沒做錯什么
Ammu, l didn't do anything wrong.
你以為我沒看見嗎
Do you think that I didn't see that?
你一直在騙我 欺騙我
You are lying and cheating me
她說要和我一起來 我拒絕不了
I couldn't say no when she said she would come with me.
所以
That's why..
所以你覺得她比我重要 是嗎
Then you are giving more importance than me. lsn't it?
不是那樣的
Nothing like that.
你為我連這么點小事都做不到
You couldn't do at least this small thing for me..
你讓我怎么再相信你
..then how can I believe you?
怎么和你結婚生活在一起
How can I marry you and live with you?
你要是再騙我怎么辦 我怎么能相信你
What if you cheat me again and how can I believe you?
我不是你想的那種人
I am not a guy as you think.
我不會騙你的
I won't do like that.
你什么都不用再說了
No, you don't need tell anything.
我不會再打電話給你了
I won't call you again.
你也不用再等我的電話了
You don't need to wait for my call.
哪里 她來了嗎
Where? Has she come?
沒有 她沒來
No, she has not come.
她沒來 為什么呢
Didn't she come? Why?
- 她看見你 生氣了 - 然后呢
-She got angry because she has seen you -Then?
然后她掛了電話 說以后再也不打給我了
She cut the call saying that she won't call me.
天哪 都是我的錯
Oh God! I did a wrong thing.
我就不該來這時辰在 是嗎
I wouldn't have come here. Isn't it?
不是的
Nothing like that.
她說是這么說 但她肯定還會打給我
Definitely she will call me though she has said like that.
走吧
Come.
你怎么知道她一定會再打給你
How do you say that she will call you again?
如果她是真心愛我 就一定會再打給我的
If she loves me truly definitely she will call me.
一定會再打的
Definitely she will call me.
怎么了
What is this?
離考試只有一個星期了
You have only one week for your exam.
你為什么不學習
Why don't you study?
我為什么要學習
Why should l study?
只有去參加考試的人才需要學習
They only will study who is going to write the exam.
我是來當你們的保鏢的
I have come here for being your bodyguard.
不是來通過考試的
Not to write the exam and get passed.
你們兩個必須好好學習
Both of you must study well.
我答應過主人的
I have promised to sir.
你不參加考試我們也不參加
If you don't write the exam we won't also write the exam.
你們為什么不參加考試
Why don't you write the exam?
因為你
Because of you.
你不參加考試 所以我們也不參加
You don't write the exam. That's why we too wouldn't write the exam
你們必須參加考試
You should write the exam.
好吧 我會參加的
Ok, I will write the exam.
不要拿著手機 認真學習
Keep the phone down and study well.
你要干什么
What are you doing?
好不容易把問題解決
Now only a problem is solved.
你還要打電話再弄出些事情來嗎
Why do you start again by your call?
你也看到他了 不是嗎
You are also seeing him. Isn't it?
如果我不打給他 他是不會好好學習去參加考試的
If I don't call him he won't study and write the exam.
就這一次
Only for this time..
就是為了讓他參加考試而已
It is only make him to write the exam.
以后再也不會打給他了
Afterwards I won't call him.
我向你保證
I promise you.
你怎么一直都沒打給我
Why don't you call me so far?
我還以為你真的不會再打來了
I thought that you wouldn't call me.
你在生我的氣嗎
Are you angry with me?
我不生氣了
I am not angry with you.
你要參加考試 所以我不想打電話來打擾你
You have exam. That's why I don't want to disturb you.
你正認真學習呢 不是嗎
You are studying well. lsn't it?
沒有 我說我不參加考試了 Meera正在生我的氣呢
No, Meera is angry with me Because l said that l won't write the exam
不參加考試 為什么
Won't you write the exam? Why?
你如果不好好學習好好考試
If you don't study well and write the exam..
我就真的不打給你了
..then l won't call you.
如果你不打給我 我就不參加考試
If you don't call me I won't write the exam.
我現在不是打給你了嗎
I have called you. lsn't it?
好好學習 好好考試
Study well and write the exam.
你拿個好名次我才來見你
I'll meet you only when you get rank.
真的嗎
Shall I believe it?
我會來的
I will come.
那這次我一定會讓你來見我的
Then this time l'll make you to meet me.
她打給我了
She has called me.
是嗎
Is it?
我說過她會打給我的
I said that she would call me.
因為她非常愛我
She loves me very much.
她說只要我考得好 她就會來見我
If I write the exam well she said that she will meet me.
真高興
Oh no..
當蝴蝶在召喚 我的花兒 不要逃
When butterfly calls, don't go, you flowers.
當我們享受愛情的甜蜜 我的人兒不要吵
Don't talk while enjoying the honey of love!
當蝴蝶在召喚 我的花兒 不要逃
When butterfly calls, don't go, you flowers.
當我們享受愛情的甜蜜 我的人兒不要吵
Don't talk while enjoying the honey of love!
你是像牙制的神像
You are the idol made of ivory!
你是黃金般的無價
You are valuable as the gold!
愛情編制的天羅地網 我已深深陷下
You've trapped me in the net of love.
當蝴蝶在召喚 我的花兒 不要逃
When butterfly calls, don't go, you flowers.
當我們享受愛情的甜蜜 我的人兒不要吵
Don't talk while enjoying the honey of love!
不知道該取什么 不知道該予什么
Don't know what to give or what to take..
我的心如孩童般左右為難上下跳動
My heart jumps over in dilemma like a child
我的頭隨你的視線而轉
Your eyes make my head turn.
我的心因你的出現而痛
My heart is aching when a girl has come to toss my life!
珍貴的回憶永無止境
Memory is valuable and never complete.
你花樣的臉龐是我的初次回憶
Your flowery face is a long first version!
我是女性的詩篇
I am the poem of the women!
你愿用自己的雙唇誦讀嗎
Will you read it with your lips?
你愿用漂亮的睫毛愛我嗎
Will you love me with your eye lash's beauty
當蝴蝶在召喚 我的花兒 不要逃
When butterfly calls, don't go, you flowers.
當我們享受愛情的甜蜜 我的人兒不要吵
Don't talk while enjoying the honey of love!
我正調到你的頻率
I am interconnecting to your frequency
當我們輕啟雙唇傾訴時 我便忘了整個世界
I forgot the world when our lips were talking
當我們互相靠近時 我便感到萬分的愉悅
If I am near you.. My heart would feel happy..
我的心跳動兩次時 我已獲得新生
I have born newly when my heart starting to beat twice
我愿在怡人的夜晚倚在你的膝頭
I will lay on your lap in the pleasant evening
我愿做紋身銘刻在你的胸口
I will become as a tattoo in your chest
明月離我雖遠 卻有美人陪我左右
The Moon is faraway.. The dame is close to me
沉浸在你的愛中 連高燒都會消退
If I drench in your love the fever will flee away
當蝴蝶在召喚 我的花兒 不要逃
When butterfly calls, don't go, you flowers.
當我們享受愛情的甜蜜 我的人兒不要吵
Don't talk while enjoying the honey of love!
你是像牙制的神像
You are the idol made of ivory!
你是黃金般的無價
You are valuable as the gold!
愛情編制的天羅地網 我已深深陷下
You've trapped me in the net of love.
電話來了
Call has come.
先問她號碼
First you ask her phone number.
再談其他事
You speak later about other matter.
說吧
Tell me.
考得好嗎
Did you write the exam well?
考得很好
I have written the exam well.
你還記得答應我的事嗎
Do you remember the promise what you said to me?
你怎么不說話啊
Why are you silent?
你會來的 是嗎
You will come, isn't it?
不 我不回來的
No, I won't come.
我沒法站到你的面前
I can't come in front of you.
為什么 我們之間有種姓障礙嗎 宗教障礙嗎 還是貧富障礙呢
Why? Do you have any problem about caste, religion, poor or rich?
就算都有吧
Assume that it's all there.
聽我說 那也不是什么大問題
Look, it is not big problem.
我想見你 你一定要來
I want to see you. You must come.
如果我來了 我就不能回頭
If I come, I can't go back.
- 我只能永遠跟著 - 你是在開玩笑嗎
-You have to take me with you. -Are you kidding me?
我是認真的
I am asking you seriously..
你愿意讓我一直跟著你嗎
Will you take me with you?
只要你來 我愿意永遠帶你在我身邊
If you come, I will take you along with me.
不要這么輕意就答應我
You don't say just like that.
好好想想再回答
Think well and tell me.
- 我父親不是普通人 - 這我不擔心
-My dad has not ordinary man. -l am not worry about that.
只要你來 我愿意永遠帶你在我身邊
If you come with me, I will take you along with me.
不管我是誰嗎
Whoever I am..
不管你是誰 不管你漂不漂亮
Whoever you are, and you are looking ugly..
只要你來 我愿意永遠帶你在我身邊
If you come with me, definitely I'll take you with me.
那明天一早你一定要去火車站
Then tomorrow early morning you have to come to railway station.
我也會去的
I will also be there.
我去不了 明天上午我要送Meera回家
I can't. Tomorrow morning I have to drop Meera in her home.
你送Meera回家的時候我就不在這里了
I won't be here when you drop Meera to her home.
為什么 為什么你就不在這里了
Why? Why you shouldn't be there?
因為我家里人也會送我回家
Our people will take me with them to home. lsn't it?
那 我和Meera說一聲
Then, l'll inform to Meera.
一個小請求
A small request!
我要通知我的父母過來嗎
Shall we inform my parents on the way?
不行 如果傳到我家人的耳朵里就麻煩了
No, if it comes to know to my people, it will be problem.
那我出發前再打電話給你
I'll call you before I start from here.
她打電話給我了
She called me.
她要我明天一早去見面
She asked me to come at tomorrow morning.
She said that she will come with me..
她說她會在她父母帶她回家之前和我一起走
..before her parents take her with them.
- 那你說了什么 - 我說我一定會去的
-What did you say for that? -l said I'll come.
你為什么那樣說
Why did you say that?
如果因為她的家人這件事搞大了呢
If it becomes a problem because of her people?
我有什么好怕的
Why should l get scared?
就算整個鎮子的人都反對我 我都不會擔心
I won't worry even if the whole town come against me.
有主人給我撐腰呢
Sir is with me.
也許我們再也見不到了
We might not meet again.
那 你和Madhu就和Amavasai和Poongodi一起回家吧
So, will you and Madhu go to your home with Amavasai and Poongodi?
好的 沒問題
Ok, I will go.
你們一起替我向神靈祈禱吧
Both of you pray to god for me.
Meera你剛才的決定是正確的
Meera, this is correct decision which you decided now.
不僅僅是為了他
You have not done only for him.
也是為了你自己
But you did for yourself too.
你大膽地去
You go boldly.
我會替你向你爸媽隱瞞的
I'll take care without knowing for your parents..
直到你們抵達安全的地方
..till both of you go to a safe place.
你出發了嗎
Have you started?
我剛出來
I just have started from home.
- 你呢 - 我正在準備
-Have you started? -l am getting ready.
我出來前必須要問你
I have to ask before I start from here.
你會娶我嗎
Will you marry me?
你問什么呢 你還不相信我嗎
What are you asking? Haven't you believed me yet?
我相信你 我只是怕
I believe you. I am asking out of fear.
要是我們見面時有什么變故
If a little change come when you see me..
我就不跟你走了
..I won't come with you.
我也不能回頭了
And l won't go back.
火車開得那么快
In running train..
別說這種話
Don't talk like this.
我說了 我不會變卦的
I have told you that you can't see any change in my face.
你大膽地出來吧
You come boldly.
我在火車站后會打你電話
I'll call you after I reach the station.
你先買兩張票上車
On that time, find the train which leaves shortly..
上往鎮子方向的末班車
..you take 2 tickets up to its last town and get into that
我會等在里面的
I will be in that.
你說過你也想見見你父母 是嗎
You told that you want to see your parents. lsn't it?
那就讓他們等在隨便哪一站
Ask them to come at any station.
我們見過他們再走
We will see them and go.
好 我會打電話通知他們
Ok, I'll call and inform them.
我會上你說的那列火車
I'll get into the train what you said to me.
如果你不在的話 那這將是我這輩子最后一趟旅程了
If you are not there that will be my last journey of life.
親愛的 那個保鏢騙了我們所有人
Dear, that bodyguard has cheated us.
他背叛我們了
He did betrayal for us.
他要和Meera私奔
He is to elope with our Meera.
他對我們家懷有敬意
He has much respect on our family.
而且為人誠實
He is a honest person.
他也知道我不會饒恕叛徒的
He knows that l won't forgive the one who does the betrayal.
哎呀 不是那樣的
Oh God! It is not like that.
是我們女兒的問題
This is our daughter's matter.
Poonkodi剛剛告訴我
Poonkodi has just informed me.
她看見他們兩人通過手機交談了
She saw them in person when they spoke through the phone.
- 出大事了 - 什么事
-Big problem has happened. -What?
你出門后不久
After you have started from there..
有一伙人沖進來綁架了Meera
..a group of guys have come and kidnapped Meera.
綁架了Meera 你說什么
Kidnapped Meera? What are you saying?
是Devaraj派來的
They are Devaraj's men.
車已經上了高速
Vehicle is going in high way.
這是車號
This is that vehicle's number.
老板有何吩咐
Sir, tell me.
你們到哪里了
Where are you now?
我們已經過收費站了
We have crossed the toll gate.
- 不要停 開快些 - 是 老板
-Don't stop on the way and come fast. -Ok sir.
- 說 - 老板 Bhoomi跟上來了
-Tell me. -Sir, Bhoomi is following us.
不能讓他靠近我的女兒
He shouldn't come near my daughter.
隨便用什么手段都行
Do anything to him.
開快點
Go fast.
嘿 開快點
Hey, go fast.
Bhoomi 不要過來 快走
Bhoomi, don't come here. Go.
聽我的 快離開這里
Listen to me. Go from here.
哎呀 老爸
Oh god! Dad!
主人 是我錯了
Sir, It is wrong what l did.
我不該就那樣離開
I wouldn't have gone like that.
我本希望有你的保佑不會發生這種事的
I wished to happen everything by your blessing.
但是我實在沒辦法
But my situation is like that.
- 原諒我主人 - 我該原諒你嗎
-Pardon me sir. -Should I pardon you?
老爸
Dad!
不要啊 老爸 不要這樣對他
No dad! Don't do anything to him!
他沒做錯什么
He didn't do any mistake.
- 把她帶走 - Karthi 聽我說 老爸
-Take her away. -Karthi, listen to me. Dad!
放開我
Leave me!
主人 我不是有意的
Sir, I didn't do intentionally.
請理解我的處境
Please understand my situation.
我已經把Meera完璧歸趙了
I've handed over Meera safely to you.
還能怎樣
Then what?
放開我 天哪 Bhoomi
Leave me! Oh God! Bhoomi!
老爸 就一分鐘
Dad! One minute!
請聽聽他要說的話
Please understand what he is going to say.
他愛上了一個女孩
He loves a girl.
那女孩說會到火車站等他
She said that she have come to the station..
所以他才離開我去火車站的
..that's why he went there to leave me.
他沒做錯你想像的錯事
He didn't do any mistake as you think.
是的 主人 那個女孩子正在火車站等著我
Yes sir. She is waiting for me in the railway station.
如果我不去 她會
If I don't go then she will..
老爸 求你了
Dad! Please..
他說的都是真的
It is true what he is telling to you.
求求你放過他吧
Please leave him.
- 好 那你走吧 老爸
-Ok, you go. -Dad!
你可以走了
You can go!
再見 主人
Bye sir!
Meera我走了
Meera, I'll go.
那個時候你的父親想到的也許只有死亡
Your dad might think only about death at that time.
如果我沒有在最后一刻登上火車的話
If I didn't get into the train at the last minute that would happen.
火車就要到站了
Station will come soon.
把你的東西收拾好
Get ready with your things.
我還沒開完會 我在下節車廂
Meeting has not finished for me. I am in next cabin.
你有多愛我的媽媽
How much you loved my mother?
你怎么突然這么問
Why did you ask suddenly?
你媽媽就是我生命的全部
Your mother is life for me.
你媽媽也很愛我
Your mother also loved me very much.
她以前和我說 在她死之前
Before her death..
她不能回Semmanoor
She has told me that I wouldn't go to Semmanoor ever
我同意了 因為你很固執
I agreed because you were very stubborn.
歡迎 歡迎 路上還順利嗎
Come. How was your journey?
你兒子呢
Where is your son?
歡迎 歡迎 我在等你們呢
Come. l am waiting for you.
來吧
Come.
主人 看看是誰來了
Sir, see who has come!
Bhoomi 是你來了嗎 過來
Bhoomi, have you come? Come.
- 主人 你躺好 - 我沒事
-Sir, you take rest. -l am alright.
坐下吧
Sit down!
我以為你不會來的
I thought you wouldn't come.
我不會拒絕你的
Will I refuse your words?
Chakrapani說你要去澳大利亞
Chakrapani said that your next posting is in Australia..
中途經過這里
..and you have come to this town in the middle.
所以我想見見你
That's why I wanted to see you.
我妨礙你了嗎
Did I give you any trouble?
主人 哪有的事
Sir, what is this? Nothing like that.
有事盡管說 主人
You tell me sir.
我以為你會來問問Meera的事
I thought that you would ask about Meera when you come here.
可你一句都沒提
But you didn't ask anything.
對不起 我忘了
Sorry! I forgot that.
Meera還好嗎 她在倫敦嗎
How is Meera? Is she in London?
還是已經回來了
Or has she come here?
Meera一直都在這里
Meera is here only.
在這里
Is she here?
那她為什么不出來呢
Then why didn't she come out?
你什么時候從倫敦回來的
When did you come from London?
你的丈夫孩子一起來了嗎
Have your husband and children come?
他們人呢 也在這里嗎
Where are they? Are they here?
Meera沒有結婚
Meera didn't marry anyone.
沒有結婚 為什么
Why didn't marry? Why?
我經常和我妻子說
I have told often to my wife.
誰娶到了Meera那真是好福氣
He'll be a lucky man who is going to marry Meera.
我沒找到那個有福的人
I couldn't find that lucky man.
她自己找到了
She found out.
但我不知道怎樣才能撮合他們
But I didn't know to unite them.
Meera 這是怎么回事
What is this Meera?
我沒想到今天見到你會是這個樣子
I didn't think that l'll be seeing you in this situation.
他們說你兒子和你一起來了
They said you brought your son with me.
他人呢 我還沒見過他
Where is he? I haven't seen him.
你知道她是誰嗎
Do you know who is she?
她就是Meera阿姨
She is Meera aunty.
可憐的Meera
Poor Meera!
她讓你爸爸去車站的時候
She didn't expect this situation..
她沒想到事情會這樣變化
..when she was lying them and sending your dad from there
老爸 求求你了 他說的都是真的
Dad please.. It is true what he is telling to you.
求求你放了他
Please leave him.
- 好 你走吧 - 老爸
-Ok, you go. -Dad!
你可走了
You can go.
他在撒謊 別相信他
He said lie. Don't believe him.
我會查清楚是誰在撒謊的
I'll find out who is telling lie.
- Palani - 老板
-Palani -Sir!
你跟著他
You follow him.
如果真像他說的 有個女孩在火車上等他 你就放過他
You leave him when a girl is there as he told in the train.
- 否則就殺了他 - 是 老板
-Else you kill him. -Ok sir.
過來
Come.
他怎么知道的
How did he know?
所有人都在問我 可我什么都沒說
All are asking me. But I said no.
很好 跟我來
That is good. Come with me.
你還要再幫我一個忙
You have to do one more help for me.
你去火車站和Bhoomi見面
You go to station and meet Bhoomi.
- 我 - 嗯
-Me? -Yes!
我爸派了人去車站
Dad has sent the men to the station.
如果Bhoomi的愛人沒有出現的話 他們就會殺了他
He told to kill him if his lover is not there.
天哪
Oh God!
所以我才讓你去
That's why I am asking you to go.
Bhoomi現在必須知道真相了
Bhoomi has to know all truth now.
告訴他是我一直在打電話給他
Tell him that I have only spoken in the phone.
但是你要告訴他不要為了我回來打架
But you have to tell him that he shouldn't fight for me..
我會等他一輩子的
..and l would be waiting for him life long.
我這么說他會相信嗎
Will he believe me if I tell him all this?
我們沒其他辦法了
We have no way.
他沒有手機了
He doesn't have phone to call.
這樣吧
Else you do one thing.
你見到Bhoomi 然后打給我
You go there and call me.
我親口和她講清楚
I will tell everything to him.
快 快走 別讓任何人看見你
Go quickly without knowing to anyone.
這是末班車 后面沒有車了
There is no train after this. This is the last train.
快來
Come.
是你嗎
Is it you?
你早就可以告訴我了
You could have told me!
Bhoomi 我
Bhoomi, I am..
老板 他說的確實是實話
Yes sir! It is true what he said to me.
有個女孩和他在一起
A girl is with him.
我背叛了Meera 這不是一個朋友應該做的
I have betrayed Meera which a friend won't do ever.
可是不僅僅是我
Not only me.
誰會愿意放過這個嫁給他的機會呢
Who will miss such an opportunity to marry him?
所以我才把你父親帶到了很遠的地方
That's why I brought your dad so far away.
因為我的背叛 上天給了我懲罰
God has given the punishment because I did this betrayal.
他功成名就后 我卻沒這個好運和他長相廝守
I am not lucky to live with him who has achieved everything. Isn't it?
我死后很久你才會拿到這本日記
You will get this diary long after my death.
你要把這本日記銷毀掉 不要讓任何人看到
You should destroy it without anyone knowing it.
因為你的父親永遠不該知道真相
Because your dad shouldn't know this truth ever.
- 怎么了 怎么還不睡 - 我睡不著
-Why? Didn't you sleep? -l didn't get any sleep.
- Siddarth 你哭了嗎 － 沒有
-Siddarth, are you crying? -No.
別騙我 你爸爸不會騙人
Don't lie. Your dad wouldn't lie.
那他的兒子就不該騙人
Then his son also shouldn't lie.
你為什么哭了
Why did you cry?
我想我媽媽了
I remembered my mother.
睡吧 我會在這里陪著 直到你睡著
Sleep. I will be with you till you sleep.
阿姨 你會生我媽媽的氣嗎
Aunty, are you angry with my mom?
生氣 為什么
Angry? For what?
我不生她的氣
I am not angry with your mom.
我只是很難過
I felt very sad.
她去世之前一直都沒說要再見我
Your mom didn't say to meet me before her death.
所以我才覺得難過
That's why I felt very sad.
你該原諒我媽媽
You should forgive my mom.
我能活著見到你和你的兒子 當面請求你的原諒
I am alive to see you and your son and ask pardon to you.
主人 別這樣說
Sir, don't say like that.
我下次再來的時候 你會很健康的
You will be very healthy when I come next time.
那我告辭了
Then, l take leave.
和阿姨說再見
Say bye to her.
那你什么時候再來看我呢
When will you come to see me again?
我能叫你媽媽嗎
Shall I call you as mom?
可以 你可以叫我媽媽
Ok, you can call me.
那你能和我們一起走 做我的媽媽嗎
Then, will you come with me as my mom?
Siddarth你在說什么
Siddarth, what are you talking?
快道歉
Say sorry to her.
我讓你快說道歉
I am telling you. Say sorry to her.
我不
I won't.
主人 對不起
Sorry sir.
他以前不是這個樣子的
He didn't misbehave like that before.
我不知道今天他是怎么了
I don't know what happened to him.
別誤會
Don't mistake me.
童言無忌
There is nothing wrong in the child's mind.
你也沒錯 可是我們
You are also innocent. But in our mind..
Siddarth問的也是我想問的
Siddarth asked her what l wanted to ask.
我想看到我的女兒幸福地生活
I want to see my daughter to live happily.
你能帶她走吧
Will you take her with you?
主人 你在說什么
Sir, what are you saying?
主人 我從來沒這么想過
Sir, I haven't thought about Meera like that.
我會聽您吩咐的 可這事
I'll obey you. But this is..
Meera你爸爸說的
Meera, what he told me..
我怎么能
How can I...?
我這輩子發生了那么多事
All these things in my life..
你愿意跟我走嗎
Do you agree to come with me?
那我告辭了
Ok, I take leave.
－ Siddarth人呢 － 他還沒上車呢
-Where is Siddarth? -He didn't come inside.
他剛才和你一起站在外面
He was standing with you outside.
旅客們請注意
Your attention please..
你去哪里了
Where did you go?
我去洗手間了
I went to the toilet.
火車上不也有洗手間嗎
Toilet is available in the train, isn't it?
帶他上車
Take him.
你去哪里了 過來
Where did you go? Come
再見
Bye.
給我親愛的兒子Siddarth
To my dear son Siddarth..
字
字幕
字幕調
字幕調效
字幕調效：
字幕調效：l
字幕調效：la
字幕調效：lai
字幕調效：laix
字幕調效：laixy
字
字幕
字幕調
字幕調效
字幕調效：
字幕調效：l
字幕調效：la
字幕調效：lai
字幕調效：laix
字幕調效：laixy